Exquisite me.
Oh.
I have an idea.
Nice.
That is a definite way to gain access.
No!
What is happening?
Go through the thing!
Bomb it!
Maybe I am angering the gods or something.
I need to get close.
I don't have a... Oh my god!
Listen to that rumble.
That's nice.
Oh my god!
What if I do it like this way?
No!
The good thing about the tentacles is, it will show you when you take damage.
It's gonna be... Yeah.
I'm scared.
I want to get off Mr. Bones while I ride.
Okay, that's getting a little too close.
It's gonna explode, isn't it?
Yeah.
I'm so fucking dead.
Oh no!
He looked different.
Fill it up with this.
Oh, that was bad.
I'm gonna die.
Oh no, the green.
The green.
What the... Is that a trap?
Oh!
What's happening?
Oh yeah.
Oh, dig for me.
Dig... Yes!
Dig for... What's this?
Concentrated mana.
Dig for me.
Go, come on.
Oh, it's just doing that.
Oh no!
I knew that would happen.
Fuck.
What do we have down here?
Yo, what's that?
Excuse me?
It's raining blood.
Hallelujah!
Whoa!
Oh my god, that's it.
Oh, it's over.
It's over.
Kill him!
Oh my god, it's over!
Oh no!
Oh my god!
See, he got a polypore into this.
Yo, what the hell?
Are you causing trouble?
Oh my god, what a shot!
Bumps for you.
Shoot that guy.
Oh my god.
Oh well.
Boom!
Wow!
Oh, I'm about to die.
Yeah, it's over.
Okay.
I don't know what I am, but I like it.
Look at all that gold.
Oh, it's catching fire.
That's a little bit sketch.
Do it anyway, do it anyway.
No, I was greedy.
I thought I could survive.
I couldn't.
Look at all that sweet gold.
But, there's a bunch of acid.
Let's hover it right above it.
Oh, that's risky.
I'm on fire now.
I'm on fire.
Fill me.
Oh no, that's confusing him.
Exquisite me.
That's for you, sir.
Wow, what a shot!
Holy shit!
I don't trust my machine gun that much.
Where are you?
Oh yeah, look at that stuff.
Looks cool though.
Oh, does he got the left?
Ah, I'm a sheep.
Fly a little sheep.
Run.
Come on, come on.
Oh
no, it's one of those guys.
What the fuck?
Is this water, isn't it?
Oh fuck, it's not.
I hit you.
Wait, he spawned a bunch?
Fuck, I killed myself.
Oh no.
Now, I'm just going deeper and deeper here.
Shit.
There's no way we're going to survive this.
I don't know what this is.
Oh my lord.
Ah, fuck.
Ah, I'm stuck.
Oh yeah, man, that's ripped.
I expected that.
We've been there.
Oops, where'd you come from?
Sir, I'm dying.
I'm almost dead.
I'm actually going to die.
Uh-oh.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck you.
Oh, no, it's over.
It's over.
I'm dying here.
Huh?
Oh, that's acid.
It's not water.
Fuck.
That scares me a little bit.
I'm going to shot him with my first one.
First.
Oh, okay.
This is the saw blade challenge with one HP.
Holy shit.
What?
Back up, back up.
Oh, he's still shooting projectiles.
Holy shit.
I may have fucked up.
Oh, shit.
I think I'm dead.
The portal is there.
I have an out if I want it.
Holy shit.
Never mind.
Hey, yo, what if I have an idea?
Hey.
Okay, whatever.
Yeah, they are angry.
Oh, he came fast.
He can pass.
Oh, no, I went up here anyway.
I'm an idiot.
I'm totally going to die.
Fuck me.
I'm being saved by the projectile repulsion field.
I'm for HP.
I don't know what to do.
I'm drowning.
Oh, that was bad.
It does.
I'm not taking damage from these.
And I take it back.
Dude, they heal.
Whoops.
Oh, what?
What?
Exquisite me?
Oh, this
thing is spawning them.
I don't like that at all.
I'm stuck.
Damn it.
I don't know what's happening.
There's something wrong with my character.
What the fuck is going on?
I'm scared of fire right now.
Oh, shit.
We're leaving.
Just go.
Fuck you, man.
Fuck you, melee.
He punched me in the.
If I touch the enemies, I die, right?
It reflects off.
I'm dead.
It's over.
Oh, there's a bunch of enemies down there.
Oh, no.
Holy shit.
We're done.
We're done here.
100%.
We're done.
There's no way.
Yep.
There's a bunch of hammers.
Wait, why is that slowing down so much?
Look at the projectiles.
Uh-oh, there's a thingy.
What the hell is happening here?
Oh, what
is it about this place?
Yeah, kill me.
Fucking kill me.
I hate this place.
I'm never coming to this place again.
I'm done.
Is that too risky?
God damn it.
This is the ultimate wand experimenter.
That's for you.
Oh, the rocks are getting absorbed.
No.
Heal me up.
Oh, but this only goes in diagonal shit.
Where'd you go?
Where have you gone?
Where did the wand go?
Oh, you fuck.
I
will not go through that portal.
I am fighting this guy with one HP.
Wish me luck, guys.
This duel is happening.
He doesn't get... show me.
Uh, no.
I take my own life.
Whoa, that's a lot of freezing vapor.
Shit.
I have an idea.
Watch this.
Oh, oh my god.
Hold on.
Oh, low, low, low, low, low.
We're gonna run a little bath here.
I'm not fucking done.
Blop.
And another bloop here.
And we're gonna blop up here.
And we're gonna blop here.
And one blop.
Maybe right here.
All right, let's try.
Call me Silma.
Okay.
Well, okay, then.
Yeah, that's...
That was... Yeah, okay.
Fair.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You like that one?
So I was timestamping all the videos on YouTube.
And of course, that obviously meant I had all the timestamps for all my deaths.
So I figured it would be cool to make a cool death montage.
When it's finally done one day, when I'm finished with the game, I'm gonna release the whole thing on YouTube.
It's gonna be fun.
How am I doing on this Friday, bro?
I'm feeling great today.
It's Friday.
How can I not feel great?
And I just ate a sandwich with some tuna, tomatoes, pesto, and what else?
That's it.
It was great.
Happy Freighters, you as well.
Bike Super 007.
We definitely need to extend that montage, yeah.
It was so much fun to make.
Just revisiting some of these old deaths make me cringe now.
It's so bad.
Some of them... I mean, I had obviously just started the game back then, but still, it's just so funny to see.
Like the one where I was underneath the cloud, thinking it was just rain and then I get electrocuted.
Amazing.
Also, I finally got the emotes to work.
Thanks to the people on Discord for linking a Reddit thread that explained how to fix it.
You will eat toast to celebrate?
Nice.
Don't forget to wash it first.
You don't want to eat it dirty.
The first ones where you couldn't even aim were painful.
I still can't really aim, but I try my best.
We're in the middle of a run, by the way, right now.
And that excites me.
You know what?
I just realized... I may have to go take a quick piss.
I should have done that before.
I'll be right back really quickly.
Okay.
All right.
You hadn't seen the one where it transformed into a mushroom and exploded?
So I was looking at that clip and what I think happened is that obviously that mushroom explodes and I walked into some fire and that made me leak and then I exploded.
So that's what happened there, I think.
Really fun.
Really unfortunate, too.
Especially that one where the enemy got transformed into some other enemy that shot blue laser ball thingies.
And that was at the very beginning of the game, so I had no way to defend myself.
Also, I was like stuck in a little cave or something.
Other new emotes?
So the new emotes are not part of the channel like that.
It's that people requested the emotes through 7TV.
It's like an extension on Twitch you can put on and then you can see emotes across all kinds of channels.
It's not related to me specifically, but it's something everyone can see if they have the emote.
Yeah.
You're making rice and chicken with bernay sauce?
Okay.
At first glance that looked like a weird combo, but I can dig it.
That sounds pretty dope, actually.
Let me know how that tastes.
Okay.
I am ready to play some Noita.
Keep exploring.
And I'm so happy I don't have to have this third party app running anymore.
I can just do the old... and then it should automatically work.
Come on.
There it is.
Yes, no crash.
And I can even switch to here.
Everything's working.
No crash.
Oh, it's so good.
So happy you guys explained that to me.
All right.
So I need to reacquaint myself here.
Also, happy Friday, everybody.
I hope you're having a great day.
Okay.
I will close you guys down.
And I'm just going to sit here and enjoy this wonderful game and find out some secrets here.
Because I have big plans.
I say that every time.
Let's just hope that I have the skills to back up what's needed to fulfill this plan of mine.
Come on.
We got this.
All right.
Let's go.
Right in the thick of it.
Let's see what I was doing.
Um, I just arrived at the jungle.
I remember that.
Hold on.
There's stuff on my keyboard.
There we go.
I have a chainsaw wand with a spitter bolt and I do this.
Oh, and then I have the digging thing.
No, this is not digging.
This is for cutting up meat.
This is the digger.
Insane.
And then we have the blood mist generator, which is also a healing pretty much because I can refill my potion with that.
It's fantastic.
I have a cool setup going right now.
So I have vampirism, fire immunity, explosion immunity, and an extra perk.
Pretty cool, I would say.
And I'm so ready for this.
What the hell is that boomerang?
Oh, I think I may have seen that before.
Energy orb.
Wait, 30 mana drain?
30 mana drain.
No, I don't want that.
The wand is also shit.
That's fine.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Actually, boomerang could be...
Hold on.
Boomerang sounds like something that could be useful when you have a healing spell.
You know, you want it to come back to you.
And hit you.
Oh, we have spiders already.
Poison.
What's that?
That is water.
Okay.
Kill that dude.
Entering some blood.
I remember I went a little blood crazy last time.
I got a little taken with the whole vampirism and all the blood that came out when you went to do this.
It's so good.
Look at that.
How's that guy not dead yet?
Unless there were multiple of them.
Oh my god.
Guys, there's also a mage or something.
Okay, one of them died.
Okay, they do need a lot of shots.
My wand is not amazing.
It's like decent, I would say.
Definitely, we can improve that later.
Okay, so here.
Let me test this wand.
Okay, not bad.
Oh, dude, it does a decent amount of damage too?
Not bad at all.
Keep a skeevy.
The digging is not fantastic, I gotta admit here.
Like, because you can't just walk and dig, you have to sort of slowly dig like that.
But that's fine.
I mean, at this point, you know, let's not look the gift horse in the mouth here.
If you go slow like this, you can definitely dig.
Oh yeah.
Nice.
Better than nothing.
We have a mine up there.
I guess this one is really good for digging through something to kill something, like this.
Like, look at the damage that produces.
That's not significant.
That is a lot of damage.
In fact, the chainsaw itself is actually a lot of damage.
Let's say you put that on a long-distance cast and you just go around chainsawing people.
Okay, that hurt.
That hurt a lot, actually.
Would you not throw that at me?
Oh, man.
Is that a glowing lance?
What is he throwing there?
So, he's not... he's like not organic, right?
Yeah, he's definitely mechanical.
No blood for me, unfortunately.
Only oil.
Gold.
Nice.
Fill up my water bottle and let's go.
Oh, there's a heart over there.
Let's get that first.
We definitely need hearts.
I feel like I have not gotten very many of those.
In this run, it's been very unfortunate.
Am
I meant to lava?
I wonder.
Nice.
There's a wand there.
Oh, and a spider too.
Yeah, the chainsaw, man.
Let's try the chainsaw on this guy.
Oh, that's super effective!
Dude, the chainsaw!
Oh, I thought that was a long-distance cast.
It wasn't.
Okay.
Bubble spark.
What about the wand itself?
I think I like the homing, though.
I mean, I wish I had Tinka with wands everywhere.
I don't have that, unfortunately.
Maybe I'll come back to that one.
Grab it later.
Also, I'm slimy as hell.
Let's get that off.
Set up here.
Get rid of that one.
Dude, I'm totally explosion immune.
I have to remember this.
Fire and explosions can't hurt me.
I'm actually insane.
Wait, what happened here?
Oh, that must have been a spider.
And blood potion.
Awesome.
Dude, chainsaw is a sick weapon.
I really need to start chainsawing things.
What if... Okay, dude, what if I put chainsaw after a trigger?
That means it chainsaws everything it hits.
Because I was trying to think, how can I make the chainsaw shoot like a normal gun, you know?
But that would be a way to do it.
Oh my god, this guy takes a lot of hits.
Uh-oh.
I'm immune to fire.
I don't care about fire.
Fire.
Come on.
Come on, bro.
Okay, we gotta drink some more blood.
In fact, I gotta find more blood.
Okay, watch this.
These guys, I can kill through the wall.
I can't take damage from my own digging thing here, right?
I don't think so.
Kill him.
Oh, yeah.
So good.
This... Dude, I have a lot of money.
What the hell?
Why do I have so much money?
We're at the jungle and I have like 4,500 monies.
Wait, did I just... Oh, I'm poisoned.
Okay.
I thought I just hurt myself with the digging mechanism.
I'm glad that wasn't the case.
Oh, wow.
He really hurts.
Another heart.
That's very lovely.
So watch this now.
Fill up my water bottle.
Oh, yeah.
It's very slow, but it works.
Like in a pinch, and you really need to heal and there's no blood nearby.
It can be used.
It's actually kind of nice.
Oh, I don't know if I'm powerful enough to try this.
I feel like I'm not confident enough for this, but I will.
Oh, hold on.
I will do this again.
Am I slippery?
I am slippery.
Okay.
That's why I'm slipping.
Let's not go up there.
That's oil.
We can burn the oil away.
Right?
No?
Oh, the oil just increases?
Weird.
Give me blood.
Wait, what?
Does it matter where I hold the flask?
Oh, I'm not so sure.
What if I were to do this?
Just spam it a bit and then we take the blood.
Oh, yeah.
It's much faster.
Look.
That's a much better way of doing it.
Wait a minute.
Wait, what?
Oh, it's blood mist.
It's not blood.
Well, oh, well, in that case, friendship ended with this one and I'm going back up to grab the other one I saw.
Fuck that shit.
Wow.
I couldn't understand what just happened.
Like, how much am I supposed to drink?
Man, what a... damn it, man.
What a scam.
The fuck?
How does blood mist not become blood when it demists?
You know?
Incredible.
Okay, let's head up here and grab this beautiful wand.
Wait.
There we go.
Yeah.
Fuck this one.
It's shite, but we do have some blood here, so that's nice.
Eat all that.
Lovely stuff.
Okay.
Drink, drink, drink, drink.
I need to saw more enemies.
I'm the butcher.
Yep.
I'm slowly getting back into it here.
Feels good.
Oh, I'm poisoned.
I'm not poison immune.
Got to remember that.
What if I were to dig this?
Oh, it's so good against the worms too.
I guess the chainsaw is really good against any organic enemies.
It's how you should look at that.
Uh-oh.
Hey, fools.
Some of them have poison and that scares me a little bit.
You know what?
This is the spot to do this.
Oh, look at that.
Look at all the blood.
It's amazing.
I feel like it's such a big deal that I discovered the whole chainsaw on the corpses thing.
Like that changes absolutely everything when you have this perk.
Vampirism.
Such a big deal.
Drink all that.
Grab more blood.
I can just keep sawing.
Just look at that.
Blood emerges.
Full on health now again.
Lovely stuff.
I do think vampirism may not be super... Oh, there's a heart here.
That vampirism may not be super great ultra, ultra late game because if you end up having like shit tons of HP, you're still gonna heal pretty slowly.
It doesn't scale with the health, you know?
So that's a bit unfortunate.
But it's amazing in the early, mid and also I would say late game too.
Not ultra late though.
Whatever that means, you know what I mean?
I think I have been in what I consider ultra late game maybe once.
I had over a thousand HP that one time.
I basically measured that by how much HP I have.
Ha ha ha.
Random damage.
Well, well, well.
Wait.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
It says damage minus 30 now.
Didn't that say damage plus 30 last time I found the random damage?
Wait, I what?
Okay, I thought the way this worked was that you put this on and every time you shoot, there's a random chance for it to do more or less.
But I guess it's like something that is specific to the spell itself you find.
So this one just rolled minus 30.
Unless I'm mistaken on that.
I'm not, honestly, I'm not, I'm not quite sure.
But I am intrigued enough to take it and experiment with it when I get to a holy mountain.
Oh no, definitely last time I shot with it.
Sometimes I did eight damage and then I did like 88.
It was super random.
But I am pretty sure it said plus 30.
So yeah.
Oh, I'm so slow with the goddamn slime.
The slime is really annoying.
Oh, what do we have here?
Quadruple and this thing.
I don't care about that.
I do care about this health though.
And the blood.
I have two blood flasks right now.
Wait, is this?
Oh, it looked a little different from the color.
It's because there's blood and all kinds of other crap in there.
Yeah, I want to dig in here.
Another reduced spread.
I don't think I'm that intrigued by it.
The wand itself is also not that great, is it?
Yeah.
I mean, it's okay.
Actually, it's actually, it's actually pretty good.
That's a good wand.
That's a really good wand.
Hmm.
Hold on, this one I have here is actually better, but it only has five slots.
That's the thing.
More slots, better.
But maybe not good enough.
I'm gonna leave it.
Oh yeah, nice.
The flowers get cut up immediately by the chainsaw.
You know what the cool thing is?
I feel like every single run...
I discover a new combination that is like super cool.
And by that, I mean new combination of a spell, I mean.
Whoop!
Like the chainsaw here is like, I've had chainsaw before, but I've never actually used it as a weapon.
I've only ever used it to increase the firing rate of my spells.
Also, I have a twitchy finger, yeah.
Blow that up.
Oh god.
Solve the corpses!
Oh man.
No, the blood is dripping.
Get it, get it, get it, get it.
Oh yeah.
There we go.
Fuck you.
Oh, oh, uh-oh.
Oh, not the fungal caverns.
My worst nightmare.
What's that?
Ooh, pheromone.
That could come in handy.
Maybe.
Nah.
Should I take it?
I think I'm gonna take it.
Let's do it.
Okay.
No, wait.
Fungal caverns.
Wait, fungal caverns.
Wasn't that?
Hold on.
I'm so confused right now.
Is that not part of, uh, the coal mines?
Why is that here?
Does it connect?
Oh no, I need to see what it actually said.
Hello, what was this?
Fireball?
No, thanks.
Did it say fungal cavern?
I'm not quite sure.
And we have pollen.
Pretty decent wand too.
Wow.
Poison arc though.
I don't like that at all.
Man, I wish I had Tinker with wands because I can't really do shit when I find a wand.
It's like, okay, cool spells there.
I can't do shit with it though.
Take care of that, dude.
The good news is, I think we may have enough to kill a god if he spawns.
Oh, there's something below us.
What?
That was close.
I spawned- Oh wait, I'm immune to explosion anyway, but I spawned an explosive boss.
Oh, I didn't even notice.
I want to dig.
No, thanks.
Slimy egg, Kiva skeevy.
Get rid of that guy.
What's that?
You know what?
Let's get the- No!
I'm an idiot!
Why do I- I threw my potion into the other potion and I broke them both.
Really good job there, man.
Great stuff.
I do love the speed up, but I love the random damage more, I think.
Although, do I?
Do I love it more?
I already have a speed up.
Let's keep the speed up.
I mean, let's keep the random damage.
Okay, let's go deeper.
Dude, I need to come to the bottom of this here mystery.
Does the fungal cavern connect from here to the coal pits?
Stop, dude.
Get sawed on.
Oh, I'm so slow.
Hey, dude.
Oh man, the fire immunity is sick!
It's actually wild.
This is actually the worst place I could be in the game, I think.
Because of all the poison, you know?
Given my current perks.
And I'm still doing all right here.
I think that's promising.
What do we have here?
These fools.
I think random damage, if it does what I think it does, on this bitterbolt would be insane.
We're gonna have to see.
Oh wait, I'm not even- I don't even care about these explosions.
You can hit me in the face with that for all I care.
Never mind, I cannot.
I just took some damage somehow.
Maybe there's some impact damage there.
Always stay full health when you can.
That's a new rule.
Wow, two wands, just like that.
Yellow glimmer?
Yo, that wand is pretty bad, never mind.
Only two slots, that makes it shit.
Now see, fire trail!
That could be fun now that I'm immune to it.
Right?
Just set everything to fire.
Burn the world.
Set the world aflame.
I think that makes sense.
You know what?
I'm gonna collect a lot of this blood right now and eat it.
There we go.
May as well do it.
Nice.
Oh, oh, oh, I'm stuck!
Oh, shit, oh, shit, oh, shit, oh, shit.
Water, water, water, water, water.
Okay, it's actually not that bad, it's fine, it's fine.
I'm gonna go saw up his corpse.
That sounds so brutal when you say it like that.
But look at that, how can you not love this?
Oh, yeah.
Delicious.
I see you there.
Get up.
Let me fill it up again.
Oh, I'm dying, I'm dying.
Okay, we're fine.
Nice.
Is that my wand?
No, that's someone else's wand.
Hold on.
You.
I don't like you existing.
Seize to exist, please.
That was bad.
You there.
Oh, yeah.
Dude, should I... I'm gonna get high.
Fuck yeah, let's get high.
Yes!
Let's see what happens.
This could be really good or really bad.
More mushrooms.
More.
I haven't had enough.
Come on.
I don't think I have enough.
We gotta find more.
What?
How much?
I'm tripping balls, though.
So, tripping balls, I thought the, my cutoff there was tripping balls, but I guess you need to do more.
Large fireball.
Yo, that's a lot of mana.
Wow.
But a very low mana charge speed.
But here's the thing.
A wand such as this could actually be really good if you have enough add mana's.
Right?
Because then you completely circumvent the mana charge speed and you suddenly have 2000 mana max.
Would be dope if I had add mana's.
But I don't.
Oh, that sound effect is cool.
Shooting spitter bolts while high.
My new favorite thing.
Also, I gotta get rid of this poison.
What?
Shit.
Oh, I'm so slow.
Dude, I'm tripping hard.
Holy crap.
Nice.
I can barely see.
Like, if there's a heart, I won't actually see that well.
You.
I'm gonna saw you and I'm gonna be completely googled up here, but that's fine.
These guys explode.
What do we have over here?
Wait, am I poisoned?
No, I'm not.
Heel up.
What is that?
Oh, that's a spider.
Oh, man.
The chainsaw is something else.
The spiders are just melting to it.
Oh, oh, oh, shit.
The big one.
I don't know.
Will the chainsaw be enough?
Those things never take damage.
Oh, this is just water.
Oh, man.
I need to make an escape route in case shit goes bad.
I don't have teleport.
We gotta have an easy out.
Dig.
Okay, let's see.
Oh, is he taking any damage?
I can't tell.
I don't think he is.
Oh, man.
No, I'm too scared.
Oh, that is.
Let's try.
Yeah, it works.
Yes, dude.
Okay, it's a little bit sketchy because you got to get in close, but it works.
It works.
It works wonders, actually.
Holy shit.
Give me this blood.
Salt the corpses.
Oh, that's more like spider blood there, but that's fine.
Ugh.
Disgusting.
I definitely need to put that on some kind of trigger or on a long-distance cast.
Something where I can reliably saw them up from far away.
You know, saw it from orbit.
I have
to remember, I do not have teleport.
Not yet, at least.
Why am I going this way?
This is sketchy.
Oh, where did you go?
Oh, he sort of buried himself in the ground.
That's weird.
Oh, nice.
More HP.
This is sorely needed right now.
It really, really is.
Cool.
Like without teleport and slimy, you are such a sitting target.
Very nice.
What do we got in here?
Oh, I'm poisoned.
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
I'm slimy.
Everything's fine.
Oh, god.
Dude, this weapon is actually almost better than my main weapon.
Like, I'm not even kidding.
This, my digging wand is the best.
Nice.
Cut up the corpses.
Drink the blood.
What the hell's going on over here?
A lot of stuff exploded and caught fire.
Oh, god.
My game is slowing down again.
Something is happening in the game right now, apparently, that the game has trouble running.
And I'm not sure what it is.
Oh, this place.
Oh, not mysterious darkness.
No, hell no.
What the fuck is that?
Oh, something.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm not going in there yet.
I'm way too scared.
I need to make a reliable chainsaw weapon before I go in there.
I tell you that.
I'm not going to go in the portal yet, though.
That seems a bit too premature.
I will get this blood, though.
Another portal.
I need to drink more of that worm blood.
I like to have been being able to see things.
In fact, worm blood is actually... I feel like I should make it a priority to always have a flask of it.
So when I find an empty flask, I'm going to actually fill it up.
And the reason is...
last time I actually discovered the hourglass.
Do you remember that?
And that was only because I had the worm blood on.
Otherwise, I would never have seen it.
So I wonder how many of those things I'm missing, like on the daily.
When I don't have the worm blood on.
I mean, I guess I could just dig everywhere, but that's a little inefficient.
What the hell?
Whoa!
Okay.
Wait.
My projectiles separate into a bundle of five explosive bolts as soon as it moves downwards.
Giga deathcross.
But these are never going to move downwards.
They just stay where you shoot them, no?
That's a weird wand.
Don't think I like it.
Another portal.
Also, notice those plants sometimes shoot different projectiles.
It's a bit random.
Okay, here we got some worm blood if we need it.
I need a flask first though.
Oh my God.
I'm stuck somehow.
Small pixel of dirt.
Okay.
I could go in here.
Oh my God.
Fucking sixth sense here.
Um, no.
That does not entice me.
Who needs worm blood when you have the senses that I possess?
Do I hear electricity?
Look how much it's burning.
Gotta find more blood.
Yes.
Imagine how much damage I would take here if I didn't have fire immunity, huh?
But then again, I wouldn't have gone in there without it.
So wait, what has been digging here?
Is that acid?
Probably.
What do we got up here?
Aha, another portal.
And a mine up.
That means there's a cave there.
This just keeps going.
What the hell?
Wait a second.
Wow.
Another one.
Wait, where am I?
Uh oh.
Nice.
I'm going to go this way.
I'm just going to keep going right here.
Oh, that looked like a heart for a second.
Too bad.
Okay.
What's up here?
I see a guy.
A guy caught
up his corpse.
Reclaim the HP he stole from me.
Fill up my flask.
Oh, this is so good.
This perk is nuts.
And now I've reached the end.
See, now I want to go this way, sort of.
What's with these flowers just blooming like that?
I don't think I understand the mechanics of those quite yet.
It's very odd.
Very thick jungle.
A bunch of worms here.
No flasks though.
Guess I could use my invisiblium.
Empty it.
I feel like that's also very good to have.
But I need to make a decision.
You know what?
No, it's not.
I have decided.
I'm going to empty my invisiblium.
I don't use it that much anyway.
Let's put it here and put it... let's make a pool here.
We can always jump in there if we need some.
Oh, absolute assholes.
Very rude.
And I'm poisoned now.
Let's cut up some corpses.
There should be a bunch.
Yeah.
Nice.
Look at all that blood.
Perfect.
Whoa!
Ouch!
That hurt.
Just wanted to get a bit more.
There we go.
Okay.
Let's move on.
Look how much money I have, dude.
Also, I kind of forgot.
Did I leave some perks untaken?
Hold on.
I have one, two, three, four perks.
And I'm in the... so hold on.
That... no, I've taken them all.
Yep.
I have not left anyone behind.
Why are these things growing when I come near?
Very mysterious.
Nice.
Look, it traps me in everywhere.
Okay, I think I may have explored most of this place now.
Obviously, there's still the luki layer and all that.
But maybe we hold off on that.
For now, at least.
Oh, nice!
A heart!
Lovely!
What's going on here?
Wait, what is that?
Oh, Ambrosia!
I thought it was gold!
That's amazing!
Yo!
Very cool!
Also, I forgot I wanted to empty my invisiblium and get worm blood.
Nah!
You know what?
I'm gonna do that before I leave.
I do like the worm blood.
It's nice to have.
I want to be able to see things.
Fuck the invisiblium.
It's also kind of a bother to put it on.
You have to throw it on yourself.
You can't just drink it, unfortunately.
A bit annoying.
Show me a good egg here, please.
I know where there were ones to the right, but let me just explore while I'm going here anyway.
Wow, what a shot!
Incredible!
This guy has aim.
There's gonna be so much blood here!
Watch!
Oh, yeah.
Yelling for days.
There's a worm.
Okay, so I'm gonna empty this over here.
I just throw it up in the air, so I also get hit by it.
That's why not.
Okay.
And now...
There we go.
And we saw him up.
And we get a bunch of blood.
I'm even gonna drink this whole thing and then fill it up again.
That's how nuts I am.
Oh, yeah.
I'm not done yet.
I'm drowning in worm blood and I love it.
All right, let's go.
Now I'm ready to see anything and everything.
All right.
Why am I so... Oh, I overate.
I see.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, look, I can see everything.
It's so cool.
A double trigger.
Very... Oh, and a teleport!
Yo, that's awesome!
That's a great wand.
Oh, glowing lance generator right there.
That's fantastic.
What's this?
Gamble.
You gain two random perks.
Gases near you ignite automatically?
That sounds pretty dope, actually, given my fire immunity, right?
Homonculus, fuck that.
Extra item, fuck that.
I'm tempted between this one or that one.
I don't know which one.
This one could become a disaster.
Let's do it!
4x instead of 2x gold is dropped when death is an accident?
Summons a luki minion to your help.
Oh, man.
Damn it.
Okay, that wasn't too great.
But let's... I guess we'll have to see.
So 4x instead of 2x gold is dropped when death is an accident.
I'm honestly still a little bit confused by that.
I think I have an idea of what's going on, but I'm not sure yet.
I may have to experiment a little bit with that.
But dude, I'm definitely getting this.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, that's right.
We have this one too.
Oh, there's so much stuff to do.
Put these ones... Ah, maybe I have too many of these.
We don't need that many.
Let's put them here and then throw this one away.
Boink.
And we buy this bastard right here.
Oh, yeah.
We now have teleport and we have this thing right here.
In fact, let's try the thing I wanted to try.
Wait, let me think.
How do I want to do this?
Let's get rid of this one and this one, that one and that one.
Oh, I thought a spider was after me, but it's my spider.
Good.
So sparkle with double trigger.
A sparkle that casts two new spells upon collision.
Am I also correct in saying that?
Wait, this one has explosive damage and an extra damage as well.
This is just a better sparkle.
It costs 15 mana.
Oh, oh, okay.
So that's the big difference there.
Hold on.
Oh, yeah.
Look, it explodes.
If I now do this, hold on.
Hold on.
I need to see if I understand this.
Okay.
Oh, wait.
I already have a random damage.
Oh, I thought that was from another run.
Oh, shit.
No way.
No fucking way.
I thought it was just a normal add damage thingy I had.
Hold on.
I do like 400, 500.
Let's put this one here and see.
That different?
I run out of mana quick.
That's like the issue here.
But hold on.
I can't tell whether or not this chainsaw is being activated on location.
Hold on.
Is it?
Oh, yeah, I think it is.
You can actually see a little spark.
You see the little yellow spark?
The yellow spark is the chainsaw.
And I guess you can confirm it over here on the board.
So it shoots a chainsaw, which is a sped up... Why do I have the speed up here, then?
Oh, because when I use this, then the speed up is still...
Isn't that just better?
Hold on.
Definitely.
Oh, yeah, that definitely shoots further.
I like that.
So when I have this here,
definitely...
Wait, why does that shoot?
Oh, because I have a double.
I get it.
I understand.
So hold on.
I need to do this.
Because chainsaw, double, it shoots these two.
Oh, but it's actually kind of slow now.
Maybe if I just remove this...
No, no, no, no, no.
Wait a minute.
Why does that do that?
So it shoots this one with that and that.
And then the next spell... Oh, but it's a double.
So it shoots this one, which is that and that, and then this one.
Right?
Uh, yes.
So the question is, though, is this actually doing anything when I add an extra one of those?
One, let's see here.
33, 33, 20, 73, 40, 33.
Okay, now add another.
30, 33.
I honestly... So I don't think this does anything.
I don't think this is helping at all in any way.
Because if this is like plus minus 30 or whatever, you know, and this is also plus minus 30, they're going to cancel out and it's going to be the same plus minus 30.
But I guess if this does add a net positive, which it clearly does, right?
Like if I add this, there's clearly a net positive.
Or is there?
Wait, I'm actually not sure about that.
33, 20.
I'm actually...
Yeah, that there's definitely a net positive on that.
Maybe.
I'm not sure.
Guys, I have no clue.
I think it's, uh, I don't know.
I like it, though.
I like it.
And I guess a lot of the damage also comes from the chainsaw.
So that's cool.
Let's put this up here.
I don't like this digging.
Unfortunately, the digging sucks.
This is actually a dope wand.
Let's put...
Do I have any digging here?
What is this one?
Ice ball.
I actually have a question.
So if this is here and it says 15, will it actually always cast it or not?
You know, that's like the question.
Or is it like always cast what, 15 times only?
And then it's, you're out of luck.
It's weird that this 15 in parentheses here, that's what I'm confused about.
So glowing lands actually costs 30 mana and this one costs 15.
And look at the damage difference.
Oh, but then we don't have the trigger, of course.
Hmm.
What if we were to put...
No, I like this.
I think I like this.
Let me try with some other spells.
Just to compare.
Let me see how much this did.
I mean, it's honestly very comparable.
This one may even be better.
No, wait, this one definitely does more.
It's also explosive damage on it.
It's very weird.
This is a very weird wand.
I gotta say, very weird.
Hold on, if I...
If I put this here...
Wait a minute.
I randomly increased the damage of the chainsaw now.
And the chainsaw is actually being shot on location.
Because, so double, one, and this one is a double, so bup, bup, bup.
I can also do this.
I cannot do that, nevermind.
Yo, that for sure does more damage.
I'm not imagining things, right?
Wait, what did I do?
I had to like... That?
Shit.
I think that's what's happening.
I think this is the one.
Yeah, look how much damage that is.
That is definite.
That scared me just now.
Stop doing that little spider.
I actually hate that the spider is following me.
So look at this.
Only five mana for that one.
So the double trigger definitely comes at a cost.
Let me try this.
Oh, what if I double trigger into one of these?
Oh, that's gonna cost too much mana, right?
Oh, that's nuts.
I wish I had an ad mana.
That's all I would like to say here.
Although we could also...
No, that's way too slow.
Yeah.
Put it back.
And let's do... I guess I'll just run with that for now.
These spells I don't care about.
And the one that I don't care about either.
So... Honestly, I may just leave it.
Bam.
We can go there.
Don't care about it.
So what else do I have up here?
Oh wait, I actually have a magic arrow with the trigger.
That's 35 damage.
No, it's 35 mana drain and 10 damage.
This is six damage, I guess.
Okay, so it's definitely more efficient.
Yeah.
Reduce spread.
I think I like my speed up.
This costs one mana, this costs three.
That could make a big difference in the long run.
Or not.
Wow, that shoots fast, doesn't it?
This is a burst wand for sure.
Oh wait, I did mean to have this one in here.
That needs to be replaced.
There we go.
That's better.
Now it doesn't bounce off either.
That's great.
Okay.
I think I'm ready to move on.
Let's go.
Go.
Up, up, up.
The vaults.
Oh man, the knockback or the recoil on this one is actually significant.
Wow, the spark bolt?
Or is it... I wonder if it's the random damage that gives the knockback.
Sorry, not knockback, recoil.
Spider, go kill him.
Let's see what you got.
Let's see what you got, man.
Kill him.
I'm not a big fan of my wand.
I gotta be honest here.
I'm not feeling it, guys.
This is not good.
Or maybe it is.
I haven't decided yet.
I really need to keep testing.
We got a wand in there.
Oh man, I need long distance cast.
Wait, what?
That cuts through this?
No way.
Yeah, this one sucks now.
Oh no, I messed up my wand.
Yes!
Fuck, unfortunately we can't go back.
That's what I need.
That's a big one, guys.
Very important.
Let's take it easy here.
Calm down.
I'm doing shit damage.
What is happening?
Or not shit.
It's like, what the hell is that?
Meteor!
Uh, I mean, that's explosive and fire, I'm guessing, so it can't hurt me, right?
I really want to try this, but it has a plasma beam orbit.
I don't know if I should try it.
I'm probably gonna die, right?
It's shuffle.
I'm too curious.
Drink up first.
Let's clear the area of enemies before we do anything foolish.
Meteor, man.
What the hell?
Okay.
Okay, this seems good.
Let's get rid of this one too.
Hey, he's trying to flamethrower me.
I'm immune, bitch!
Can't hurt me.
Wait, what?
Oh, bring some blood.
Yeah, I hate my wand.
It's almost like my shots are penetrating the enemies and going through them and then not hitting them.
It's weird.
Very weird.
All right, let's try the wand.
Oh, dude.
I wonder if that one works with infinite spells.
If that's the case, I'm gonna go nuts with that spell.
It's gonna be sick.
Wait, what?
Oh, oh, it's one of those teleport thingies.
It's the one I died to once.
I need to get in water.
There we go.
Those things are dangerous.
Especially when you have spells that hurt yourself.
Oh, don't go swimming in the thing.
No water!
Where's my water at?
Am I gonna fucking die here?
Blood,
blood.
Oh my god, man.
That was brutal.
Oh, this wand is so bad now.
It's actually unreal.
I made it so much worse.
I don't understand how I'm so bad at this game.
How did I make this so much worse?
God damn it.
Oh, well, blood we have enough of.
That's something.
Get all that blood.
I guess the good thing about this wand is that when I shoot enemies, they instantly get sawed.
So blood just pops out.
Maybe I understand why some of my runs have been so bloody now.
It's because I have been sawing them without knowing it.
It makes a lot.
It explains a lot.
Oh no.
Okay, that's fine.
Okay, let's get in here.
This spider is the worst thing ever.
Like, what a shitty perk.
Oh, I have to remember, I still have this thing as a weapon.
That's a decent weapon.
Maybe I'll start using that.
This will be my main driver.
What
is that?
0.75 projectile speed.
Damn.
Maybe I'll take it.
Let's try it.
Spells per cast.
So I'm just going to shoot in a random direction a black hole with a lot of projectile speed.
But less damage.
But that's fine, because it doesn't do any damage anyway.
Let's see.
Oh, but wait, it's shuffle.
It's shuffle, so it's... yeah, okay.
Well, rip.
I'm definitely taking it though.
That's a lot of black holes.
That seems like a good one to have.
What is all this?
Energy sphere?
No, thanks.
Not intrigued by that.
Okay, another heart.
Very welcome sight.
Nice.
I am really surprised I can cut through the steel with this.
I have gained a new respect for the luminous drill.
I need more water.
What if I destroy that?
I'm just gonna pop up with a bunch of freezing vapor here.
Yeah.
Yep.
Oh no, it's way too poisonous.
Ah, fuck.
I ran out of levitation.
Get up here.
Ah, come on.
Oh, I didn't mean to pick that up.
Fuck.
All right, that's fine.
Grab some health.
I mean, water.
I can't do anything here.
Fuck.
Oh, but you know what I could do?
I'm gonna leave this wand here and come back for it later.
Uh, let's... oh, should I leave it here though or take it with me?
Okay, I will leave it here and I'm gonna make a note so I don't forget because this is a crazy wand.
Let's leave it right here and I'm gonna write my notes.
Uh,
here we go.
Let's say...
I'm just gonna write current run.
Notes for this run.
A bit too small.
Current run.
Uh, I am currently in the vault.
In the vault.
Uh, wand.
With black holes.
I will never forget it now.
Okay, let's move on.
Now we can grab even more cool wands and then we have to anchor the gods at some point.
But that's fine because we have to go back, right?
That's the whole plan.
So we just have to figure out a way to deal with that.
That's fine.
This guy though is annoying me.
Nice.
No, I think this wand is actually good.
I think the reason I hate it so much right now is because it runs out of mana so quick.
Like for me, that means it's such a big deal for me.
When I can't just hold it down, it really does feel a lot more worse.
You know, so I think the wand is fine.
I just need to calm down here a bit.
Okay, nice.
Add mana.
Wait, didn't I find that somewhere else as well?
Wait a minute, didn't I find add mana on something?
Anyway, I'm taking that.
What is going on there?
Is someone shooting propane tanks?
I guess he must have killed himself.
Someone was definitely shooting propane tanks.
Damn.
I just see tanks flying around.
The scariest thing you'll ever see.
You know what also is scary?
Electricity.
Speak enough.
That's electrified.
Yeah, you know what?
No, I don't have the courage.
Oh, is that thing in there?
I'm gonna blow it up.
That's right.
Stop your electrifying ways.
Why is it still electric?
What's happening?
Is there a Ukuskivi in there?
That word is just in my nightmares lately.
Oh, hold on a second here.
Blood!
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I'm drowning in blood.
Look, I can come back here anytime and heal.
Absolutely incredible.
Oh, no, don't overflow.
Oh, why did I do that?
I'm kind of an idiot.
That's okay.
We like when it rains blood.
It's a good thing.
I thought I just uncovered a spider, but it was my friend though.
Okay.
Also, I'm gonna drink some worm blood.
That way we get to see.
Show me the secrets.
I guess it makes more sense to put on the worm blood when you're at the edge of the map, where they usually hide secrets.
That guy is really loaded.
What was that?
Oh, hello.
What's happening there?
Why is there green stuff falling out of the air?
Look at that congregation in there.
Oh, I'm going to be digging these guys.
Watch this.
Oh, yeah.
Isn't that amazing?
I think it is.
Incredible.
So, I've been here.
That's the one with the ad mana that I found.
You know what?
Let's bring that one back too.
So, I'm gonna bring both of... Oh, no.
Okay.
So, that one is here.
Let's remember this.
So, I go up and left.
We're making a whole cache of stuff to get later on.
It's like when you're digging down beers in the woods, you know?
You make a little hole and dig down some beers so they can be cooled by the earth.
Same idea, but it's with wands and it's in a mountain.
I'm gonna leave this wand and that wand.
There we go.
Look at this.
The trio of amazing things.
I'll come back to you later, lovelies.
I'm gonna put that in my notes too.
I'm just gonna... Also, 2x ad mana.
Nice.
Then we go pick up our other wand, which should be...
Where is it?
I think maybe somewhere here.
Nope.
Wrong spot.
Further down, I think.
Oh yeah, down through here, I think.
Uh, yeah, I totally don't know where it is.
Fuck.
It was down and right.
It's not here because I haven't been here.
I went this way.
I remember this.
Did I go further up here?
No, I didn't.
Wait, what the... It's... Oh, here it is.
Nice.
Got it.
Okay, that's a bunch of electricity that scares me.
What is causing that?
Let's try and get to the bottom of this.
Is it you?
Oh, it was an enemy.
No, wait.
What's that?
Oh, I can't pick it up.
I thought it was an Ukuskivi.
But I don't think it was.
Don't you snipe me.
Oh, you didn't even die.
Where's the laser?
There.
Snot balls.
Uh-oh.
Scary enemy.
How are you not dead?
There we go.
What's up, guys?
Oh, there's stuff everywhere.
Just calm down.
Stand your ground.
Just slice them up when they come close.
It's actually really good at this.
Like, they just fall into my beam.
Uh-oh, I'm frozen.
Okay, we're fine.
Oh, wow.
So chainsaw is really shit against mechanical opponents.
It makes sense.
Oh, what's going on there?
That water was balancing on a chain.
That doesn't make too much sense.
I mean, maybe the 2D world it does.
Yeah, I guess it does in the 2D world.
Oh, shoot.
That was a bit sketchy.
I'm doing pretty good, actually.
I think the one is slowly growing on me a little bit.
If I can add the add mana to it, I think it's gonna be great.
We may just need a bigger one, though, because I'm running out of slots on this one.
I don't need the both random damage, I don't think.
It's a bit too much.
With only one add mana, that should be enough.
Because this thing is costing like 15-something mana per shot.
Oh, shit.
That was a bit too sketchy.
This guy has so much HP.
What?
He's a Jedi!
Wow!
That's a hard enemy.
I need blood.
Okay.
Constantly taking damage here.
Man, this spider companion is shite.
It does nothing.
Useless.
Get some water.
That's acceleration.
What do we got?
An egg.
I mean, I'll take it because I don't have a fourth wand, so I guess we'll do it.
I gotta say, this is my favorite wand for dealing with the little bitty enemies there.
It's so good.
No thanks.
I need to find blood.
Whoa, what's happening here?
That thing was filled with something.
There's a wand down there as well.
I think I may have checked that one.
Let's double check.
Oh, yeah!
Hold on.
Ten mana drain.
Three damage, one trigger.
This may actually be good.
I'm taking that.
May actually be better than the double, just because of the lower mana usage.
But then again, if we get the ad mana later on, you know...
Oh, not this guy again.
He's actually an issue.
At least we have a lot of blood here.
Hey, you there!
Come here.
Dude, I'm dying.
This is an insane enemy.
Okay, let's get some blood.
I think I'm taking damage from some assets somehow.
What am I taking?
Oh, I'm poisoned!
Oh!
There was poison in there.
Okay, I'm not going in there again then.
We gotta find blood.
I have to find that vat of blood I had earlier.
The big pool of it.
It was somewhere on the right side, I think.
Get out of here.
Yeah, I'm not sure where it is.
Maybe I'll find it, maybe not.
But now I'm just gonna keep exploring.
Okay, we got some blood here.
That's something.
Drink, drink, drink.
Oh yeah.
This guy I can cut up.
Okay, the spider was doing some work there, I think.
I saw a bunch of damage numbers.
Not sure how much damage it really was.
It wasn't bad.
Uh, cut him up.
Oh no, the blood is gonna fall into the lava.
Oh!
Dude, imagine in this run, if I got high, and all toxic sludge became blood.
Holy shit.
Wouldn't that be insane?
That would be completely insanity.
Okay, I see you up there.
How are you not dead yet?
There we go.
Unfortunately, he doesn't bleed.
Blood.
Nice, a big pool of blood.
I think that's almost full HP.
Ah shit, not when I get shot at!
Assholes.
Oh my god!
There we go.
I also cut up those corpses.
It's gonna be a real feast.
Okay, I'm gonna do that now.
Can I kick it over there?
Oh yeah, oh yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
Nice, we're back on top, baby.
We are back.
Wait, am I cutting away the meat with the green laser and actually removing it?
I'm not entirely sure.
Hopefully not.
Again, I thought my companion was an enemy.
Come at me, come at me.
Amazing.
Come here.
You know, this one is so good that if you hit the main guy with it, all the little spawns it makes die instantly.
So good.
I hear electricity.
It's you!
Let me drink some more worm blood.
I see wand.
I see chest.
Exciting.
Nice!
Exactly what a man needs.
Oh, this electricity is so scary.
Is it you?
It is!
It's just causing every nearby metal to be electrocuted or electrified.
Kind of a scary enemy now.
It does feel like I'm a little bit high when I have worm blood on.
Maybe it does give you a bit of a high.
Okay, let's see what we got.
Homebringer.
Yeah, how about no?
Nah, the one's not that great.
Don't like it.
Or do I like it?
Wait a minute.
Huh.
No.
Nope.
I think before I go through the portal, I'm gonna grab one of the add mana wands.
Because I think that's the biggest thing I can do to make this wand be a lot better.
In fact, let me grab it now and just head through the portal.
We are going now.
Unless I find something on the way, you know, something I can be distracted by, then I'll quickly take a look.
But the plan is to go grab the wand now and get out.
Oh, hold on.
We've got another wand.
It was happening?
Why is he...
Okay.
It looked like he had a circle of stillness on him.
Somehow.
There we go.
And the wand itself is not terrible either!
I'm taking that for sure.
Definitely taking that.
Let's not mess up now.
Stay full HP.
How rude!
How are you not dead?
Oh my god.
All this poison!
Or acid.
Or toxic.
I don't know.
Fucking same thing.
Green bad things.
Although, poison is actually purple.
That's the exception there.
What the hell?
Spider?
Oh, I think the chainsaw is doing work here!
Uh-oh.
Wait, I'm immune to that.
I'm immune to your shenanigans.
Wanna shoot missiles?
I don't care.
Again?
Okay, I'm gonna head up here.
I guess this is a way back?
For now, at least.
Okay.
Oh, hold on.
There's a wand here.
Oh, I've seen that one already.
Cool.
I keep thinking that's an enemy.
Uh-oh.
It's a teleport guy.
What the fuck?
Is it...
Okay, is it when I hit him?
Or is it something he does just...
Is it just...
Fucking...
I can't speak English.
Hold on.
Okay, there we go.
Is it, like, completely coincidental that I just teleport whenever I shoot?
Maybe he hits me at the same time.
It felt like it's...
It happened when I hit him.
And not when he just decided, you know?
Oh, no.
These guys are the worst.
Okay, my spider is distracting him.
Hey, spider, bro!
You actually did something.
Incredible.
Okay, bro.
Oh, that's very bad, man.
Charge speed, but with an add mana.
This could...
Oh, spells per cast, seven.
Yikes.
I'm not sure about that one.
I do kind of like the wand, and I think I like it more than...
Hold on.
I think I may bring it back to my lair.
Let's bring it back to the lair, and then come back and grab this one after.
Back to the lair!
Uh, let's not go that way.
Oh, wait.
Uh, wait, where are we right now?
Oh, wait, I have a great way back.
Check this out.
Easy.
And then we put it here.
Another wand to the collection.
There we go.
Off we go.
It's fine blood.
Now to remember where my wand is.
If I can find...
Okay, I know exactly where it is.
Or do I?
There it is.
Nice.
Oh, yeah, wait.
I wanted to go back anyway to grab the...
See, now I'm conflicted, because I have the healing on this.
Man, this is such a bummer.
I need to be able to...
Okay, I have 15,000.
I may have a plan here.
And the plan is, I'm gonna go to a holy mountain.
I'm gonna keep rerolling perks until I get the one I want.
And I realize chances are not on my side here, because the price is doubling every time.
It's kind of a bad plan, but it's a Hail Mary I'm willing to do.
Otherwise, we just have to...
figure out a way to dig.
And we can dig, actually.
With that, earthquake shot.
Okay, the plan is forming.
The plan is...
Hold on, this is getting a little too chaotic.
It's getting scary.
Rid of the fucking toxic.
Take care of the enemies.
Okay.
Better.
Is this a shitty wand?
No, thanks.
What's happening here?
A bunch of this is burning away.
That pleases me greatly.
Okay.
Oh no, not this dude!
Come on, spider, kill him!
Fucking do something!
Useless perk.
Okay.
What's this?
No.
Nope.
Nope, nope, nope, nope.
Oh my god.
Finally.
Uh-oh!
Uh, I'm stuck.
I'm late to fight!
Oh, that could have been really bad.
I could have died.
We gotta find blood.
Oh my god!
What are the chances?
Have you teleported into one of those?
You get shocked!
That's scary as hell.
Hold on, is this just evaporating on its own?
Wait, something just took 2,700 damage.
Is that my minion?
Hold on.
I have healing bolts.
Oh, but it has earthquake shot on it.
That's not a thing to do right now.
That seems like a terrible idea.
In fact, this place is no good.
We gotta go back and find all that blood.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
What is going on here?
This is not the way.
We have some blood here.
And something.
That a corpse?
Jesus!
He was waiting!
Where's the big bath of blood?
I'm pretty sure it was somewhere east.
Somewhere over here, maybe.
Not up there.
Somewhere here?
Yeah, that works.
But it's not the place I was thinking of, but that's fine.
This is gonna do the job.
Some of the job, at least.
Okay, let's move.
That is not the place.
This is not the place either!
Getting out of there, that's for sure.
Where's this massive reservoir of blood that I made?
Oh, there's some here.
I'll take it.
Better than nothing.
Okay, I gotta say, so vampirism is nice, but it is a little tedious when you don't have any blood at hand.
It's like...
It's not amazing.
Let me say that when you're in this situation here.
Definitely could be better.
What's going on inside of that place here?
Whoops!
I thought I was using my digging wand!
I was using this!
I could have killed myself there.
That was really close!
What is that?
Why is there a plus there?
You see that?
What?
What the hell is going on?
It's gone now.
Okay, give me more blood.
Drink, drink, drink.
It's the slowest healing ever.
Ah, here we go!
That's it!
Beautiful.
Full health incoming.
Oh yeah, that's beautiful.
Ah, lovely.
That's lovely, that.
That's lovely, isn't it?
And we're full.
Okay, so the plan is to...
Uh, let me think.
So this healing is nice, but it's not really needed.
Because I have vampirism.
So I'm gonna go back and exchange this wand for the cast...
Or the add mana wand, and then I'm gonna head out of here.
That is the plan.
And what a plan it is.
Here we go.
Which one do I want?
That one or...
Let me see this wand.
Yo, this wand is sick.
Like, the stats on that is actually dope.
So is this one.
But this one has more slots.
I'm taking that.
Yep, thanks.
Alright, let's head out of here.
To the portal we go.
Sup, dude.
Oh, we also have blood here.
Good to know.
Here we are, let's go.
Okay.
Why is my wand black?
Look at that.
Weird.
Okay.
Another one of those.
What the hell is that one?
Spells to power.
Converts any nearby projectiles cast by you into extra...
Damage?
Wait, do you mean like...
The more I shoot, the more damage I do?
So the faster wand I have, the...
This one is nice, but I don't want it.
I'm rerolling.
Phasing.
How is this not completely broken?
I feel like...
How is that not insane?
That's got to be a catch to this.
This to me sounds like you're immune to damage.
It's like you can only take melee damage?
There's no way.
I mean, I got to try it, of course, before I make up my mind about it.
Melee immunity is nice, but dude, I'm looking for...
Either peace with gods or tinker with wands everywhere right now.
But I guess I can't keep rerolling forever.
It's gonna be costing way too much money.
Maybe melee immunity is the way to go.
I think it's the solid choice to make.
I think it's solid.
Okay, now.
The big moment.
Let's see how much this will do.
And we want to double dip this one.
So that means we put it here.
And then we have this here, which is gonna...
Wait, we only need maybe one of these.
Let's see now.
Oh wait, did I...
That's what I'm fucking talking about, baby.
Now we're rolling.
And then we use this.
Like the speed is a little...
Wait, why is my...
Oh, I think the audio is bogging a little bit here.
Maybe I don't want that.
I mean, the damage is nice.
But I'm not so sure about the actual projectile here.
What's this?
Big magic guard.
Eight guarding lights rotate around you for a time.
Hold on.
Remind me exactly what happens there.
And they get absorbed.
They absorb spells or...
Oh no, wait, I remember.
It actually hits enemies.
It hits...
It actually damages enemies when it passes through them.
I think I tried that once before.
So hold on a second.
0.15, 0.45.
790.
This one is not even bad either.
What about this?
It's not as cool.
I mean, I always come back to this fucking spell.
The triplicate bolt is just better than everything else.
Okay, maybe not like that.
Maybe we put this here and then there.
Okay, now it's not actually doing much damage.
But that's because we don't have this.
Maybe we don't need to speed on it.
Okay, you know what?
It's about equal.
Oh, look at this.
Why is this not showing damage?
Maybe a large spitter bolt.
That's pretty dope.
With speed?
Oh, that's very inaccurate.
Why is it so inaccurate?
I don't know what I like most.
I don't like recoil.
I guess this one is the lowest recoil, I guess.
I mean, this is not bad.
This is actually fine.
I'm gonna leave it like this.
We definitely improved this wand.
And, hold on.
It's shooting that.
It's shooting this one and then two more.
That one and that one.
But hold on, we're not...
Yeah, we are double dipping on that.
Look, one ad mana there.
And then one ad mana there.
In fact, this is doing three things.
It's shooting a chainsaw by its...
Oh, this is the one he shoots by itself.
Now it's super slow.
Let me try something real quick.
Instead of having...
So, that's like...
Okay, now let me change this around.
To here.
Oh, wait.
There.
No, it's not better.
That's fine.
I mean, it's a fine wand.
It's a fine wand.
What can I say?
Okay.
Then we also have a bunch of things.
Do we want anything from here?
Maybe not.
I don't want any of this either.
In fact, I'm very unhappy with these spells and these ones.
Very unhappy.
It's not my style.
I'm gonna move on.
Time to kick some ass here with infinite mana.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm affected by...
What's it called?
Neutralized spells.
That's a terrible debuff.
Absolutely horrible.
Don't hit me.
Die, please.
Thank God.
Okay.
What is my mission in here?
My mission is...
What is my mission?
I wanna...
I wanna find a digging wand that can, once again, take me up top.
And then we're gonna have to deal with the gods.
It is what it is.
Because I have some black holes and stuff that I can dig with up top.
I just need to get up top, basically.
Question, though.
Oh, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
This one doesn't go through dense.
There's no way.
What?
Wait.
That works?
Wait, what am I...
What if I've been smoking?
Why did I think this didn't work?
What?
I'm confused as fuck right now.
Never mind, we can go up.
Has this always been able to do this?
That's crazy.
Oh, we're gonna be angry.
We're gonna be making people angry now.
What do I have to deal with it?
Hopefully my wand is good enough.
That's all I'm gonna say.
Hopefully it's good enough.
Fuck it, we're angering.
Wait a minute.
Is that the same sound?
Hold on.
This is just the liquid in here, right?
Oh, you know what?
Drink this.
Oh, yeah, it is.
It just sounded like...
It sounded like one of those...
Like orbs.
I thought that maybe it was an orb here.
In fact...
Wait a minute.
Doesn't that kind of look like...
The eye in the...
Oh, what's it called now?
The fucking thing with the sand in it.
The hourglass.
Is that the same symbol?
That thing was glowing, wasn't it?
How come the gods are not angry?
Hello, I'm destroying property!
Sir?
Come on, dig that little pixel, please!
Thank you.
Oh, you know what?
And now we deliver blood to the holy mountain.
Amazing.
Don't want to get into the peat.
Do you want to pick up more blood, though?
Give me this.
Oh, yeah.
Full on blood.
Okay, awesome.
So...
Oh, but wait, we can't edit any wands.
It's so painful.
Not being able to do that is actually...
Just the worst.
I can't believe I can dig with this.
Dude, I could have made my way through the mountains without angering anything.
I mean, with angering people, but being able to edit later on.
Fuck!
Well, I'm glad I discovered this now, at least.
This is actually a big deal, you know?
That I discovered that.
Oh, man.
That's just unreal.
Get rid of that.
Okay, which one do I bring?
Probably this one.
Yeah, I like that one.
Man, why is this thing here, you know?
Fucking hexagon.
Get it out of there.
Nobody wants that.
Like, look at this.
I could have just done this.
I thought, since day one, ever since I found this, I'm pretty sure it tested it on the brickwork.
And it never worked.
But maybe it's just because I always tested it when it was super slow.
You know, when it went ding, ding, ding, ding.
It basically never did anything.
And I just assumed, oh, it's not doing anything.
When in reality, all you needed to do was just keep going.
Insanity.
I could have just taken that portal, by the way.
But that's okay.
Okay, so at least we now know how to do this in the next holy mountain.
That's the only place we can edit or want.
What a disaster.
So we have to go back there every time.
I may actually just go straight to it right now just because I want to edit once.
And I can get back.
Yeah, you know what?
Let's go find a portal.
Let's do it.
Whoa!
I wish I had two HP less.
That's my maximum.
That is my wish.
I have gained new respect for the luminous drill.
I thought I was shied up until today.
See, that's the thing I learned this run.
This is like the big discovery this run.
It's like the biggest, for sure.
It will change everything going forward.
Okay, can I also go through here?
Oh my gosh.
Too bad he bleeds sand.
I'm stuck!
Holy shit!
I could have died there.
I was totally stuck.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Do any of these guys bleed blood?
Or is it all slime?
That would be a disaster.
Oh no.
These guys are the worst.
How about a chainsaw?
He doesn't give a fuck.
Well, I guess there's a chainsaw on my main want.
What's hiding in the sand?
Nothing, huh?
Actually, it's just digging just as well.
Oh yeah, it's digging even better.
Also, I think I'm immune to his attack, because it counts as melee.
No, wait.
I'm not sure.
I think I took some damage.
Not entirely sure.
Let's grab some water.
I'm low HP here.
I need to...
I need to heal.
I'm gonna go find some blood.
Okay, there's a little bit here.
Not a lot though.
Aha!
Nice.
And that all came from the level above.
Oh, look at this.
Beautiful.
I think I'm drinking a lot of water here too.
Oh, this is mostly water.
Yeah, shit.
That's bad.
Empty it.
I'm fully satiated.
Not a thing you want to be.
Okay, let's head to the portal.
That is such a good digger.
On sand at least.
I keep thinking I have to spam it just shortly, because I don't have mana, but I do have mana now.
Gotta get used to that.
Does it also look like my spells are going through the enemies?
Like, it's...
Or maybe I'm just missing some of the shots.
Like they're going above their heads or something.
Stop spewing that crap.
Ah!
I think the audio is starting to bug out a little bit.
Maybe it's time to restart soon to fix that.
I also think my wand is bugged, because it's all black, look.
Like there's a graphical glitch on it.
Oh yeah, sweet money.
Reroll money is what that is.
I need to find more blood.
Oh wait, there's actually a lot here.
Yes!
Beautiful.
Now we keep filling it up.
Massive.
I'm gonna go down here.
Oh no, not these fuckers again.
Wait, what?
I thought I made that somehow.
I thought I had picked up a wand without knowing it, and then shot that off somehow.
Very cool.
Oh wait, the green one is the toxic shit.
We don't want that.
Or the cursed.
Yeah.
Leave me alone.
Oh yeah, the audio is definitely starting to bug out a little.
Bastard.
Okay,
this one is actually sick now.
See?
I had a feeling.
It was only the mana issue that made it shit, you know?
Like the wand itself was fine.
The fact that I could only shoot it for a couple seconds is the thing that made it not fine.
Okay.
Trap.
Okay, I'm gonna restart real quick, just to fix the audio.
Um, I have this feeling that maybe it'll crash.
And I'll have my save ruined again.
Speaking of, I think I may need to back up my save folder, just in case people were saying there is a chance one of these crashes can corrupt everything.
And that scares me a little bit.
So I think after this stream, I'm gonna make a backup of absolutely everything.
Just to be safe.
Oh, there's so many enemies!
Dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude.
Calm down, calm down, calm down.
Drink some blood.
Oh, there's so many here.
This is wild.
Go hide.
And now we cut up the corpses.
Oh, look at all the money.
Oh, yeah.
Hold on, something's stuck on my teeth.
Ah!
I was touching my face!
I do wish there was a keybind, so I didn't have to right click up here.
I can just click something on my keyboard to drink the equipped flask.
Hold on, maybe there is.
Let's look at this.
Use wand.
Interact, maybe.
I don't think so.
No, E doesn't work.
Okay, that's fine.
I mean, it's fine.
Just a minor thing.
A minor quality of life, that would be nice.
Especially when you're a vampire like me.
Oh!
Okay, you know what?
I've noticed something.
When you drink blood in...
Oh, I forgot to note down the name of this place.
The art, I think it's called.
There's always a cloud that appears above you.
It's like drinking blood in this region is...
Doing that for some reason.
And I'm not sure why.
Okay.
Okay, let's go.
Let's see what perks we got.
This is our last chance.
Show me something good now.
What is that one?
Blood to power?
That sounds promising as hell, given our current...
Giga white hole?
Yo, hold on.
I'm way too intrigued by this.
Let's see what we got here.
Farms materialized, exploding gold, freeze-field, trick blood money.
Blood money's...
No.
Worm attractor?
No?
No.
We roll again.
No?
Revenge?
Revenge explosion?
Nope.
Unhappiness?
What's that?
Revenge bullets?
Dammit.
I'm not getting what I want.
No.
Aw, man.
I'm not gonna have money for my thing over here.
I'm gonna prioritize the perks, though.
What's that?
Healthy exploration?
Oh, that's the one I don't care about.
All seeing eye?
Hmm.
You know what?
That is not terrible.
So this run is not, like, amazing or anything at this point.
But this one could be nice to discover secrets in this run, at least for future runs.
I'm taking it.
Let's do it.
And now I don't have money for this, unfortunately.
I really wanted to see what this was.
Lots of power seems incredibly promising.
I'm gonna guess that it's...
Oh, can I have a see what it is?
No.
I'm gonna guess that it's something like the more bloodied your clothes are, the more damage you do, or something.
Eming arc.
Dark flame.
13,000.
Yeah, I don't have money for any of that.
All right, let's go, dick.
And we're gonna...
Oh, hold on.
Yeah.
We're not gonna collapse this place.
This is our place where we can edit.
So let's do that now before we leave.
So light shot...
is actually amazing on a black hole.
Because, watch.
This is gonna be insane-o style.
Oh, they're angry now.
Oh, here he comes.
You wanna fuck with me?
Oh, yeah, you hate that, don't you?
Fuck you.
Wait, am I immune to his damage?
Or is it just the explosive effect of his damage?
There we go.
No problem at all.
Taken care of.
The gods are nothing.
Okay.
Up we go.
Let's see how much this dug.
Damn!
Yo, that's wild.
Dude, we can- hold on.
That's insane.
We can make it even more crazy.
Watch this.
I wonder if, like...
So, is this multiplicatively stacking?
Meaning, if this is- if this is multiplied by 7.5 first, and then that number is multiplied by 2.5, that would be insane.
Because that would mean this is going insane-o style fast.
Let's see it.
Oh,
that thing flew off!
Damn!
Okay, uh, wait a minute.
Let's see here.
Let's change these around.
The hell is that?
Wait a minute.
What's going on?
What the fuck is that?
It's some kind of...
sarcophagus?
No, it's like a statue.
What the hell?
Oh, wait, something's shooting.
Uh-oh.
Careful here.
Let's put a bunch of these up here now.
Uh, this is my storage.
Um, hold on.
I wish I had a bigger wand, so I could do this thing I'm doing here, but with all of them, so I didn't have to go back and exchange it every time.
Maybe I will disregard the teleport for now, and have a digging there.
I think that's more important right now for me.
This one can go there.
Let's just organize this neatly.
Put the empty ones in the back.
Okay.
Uh, 9000 gold.
I could also take a...
Oh, yeah, wait.
I can take spell refreshers on the way up, I guess.
All right.
Let's head back up.
Let's see how much this dug.
So I shot one black hole.
Here, let's see how far up it went.
Oh.
Ah, you bastard.
Yeah, look, it's teleporting every time I shoot it.
What an asshole.
So basically, he's swapping places with me whenever I shoot him.
Which explains, and this is what I theorized back then as well.
You remember the wand death I had?
I had the modifier on my wand that made it damage me too.
So I hit him, we switched places, and what's happening here?
Oh, there we go.
We switched place...
Oh, don't go in there.
We switched places and then I hit myself.
Also, I need to get blood.
Hold on, I can just go little nuts here.
I can...
Maybe, maybe let's not go two nuts.
Actually, let's go nuts.
Let's go see if that triangle's over here.
Wait, why is my...
Am I all seeing eyes not doing shit?
I thought I could see everything.
What a scam.
What is this, man?
Hey, I'm disappointed.
What the hell, man?
I was hoping I could see, like, the whole screen.
Oh, shit.
Now, see, now I miss my teleport.
Unless, hold on.
Ah, this does give me a little bit of a good lift.
There we go.
Oh, yeah, look.
It's actually much harder to hit with this one without the speed up on it.
I just need to get used to it.
What I'm gonna try here...
Oh, actually, hold on.
There's a slimy egg there.
Look at this.
There's an egg here and a slimy egg there.
What are the chances this is the one I need?
This guy's my friend now for some reason.
Let's put this one down gently.
And kill this guy over here, too.
Oh, no, the egg broke!
This is where he came from.
Fuck me.
God damn it.
Whatever.
Speaking of eggs, you know what?
Let's try it.
It does have an electric arc that...
It's a little bit scuffed.
But I'm gonna try it anyway.
I need something eggy.
Hey, hand over your money.
I actually need money.
I need a lot of money.
Also need blood.
Let's see.
A bunch of friends spawned.
It actually works!
Oh.
Oh, no.
Oh, shit!
Like all that shit.
Oh, wait, it costs mana.
Hey, that works!
Fuck your shit.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Oh, no, oh, no, oh, no, oh, no.
What the fuck is going on here?
This is evil.
Evil brickwork.
I'm losing a lot of HP.
I can die, I can die, I can die.
What the fuck is going on?
Okay, they dropped spells.
I'm out of black holes, though.
I'm out.
Um, new plan.
New plan.
Where's our wand?
Oh my god, he's destroying everything!
Oh, here it is.
Grab it.
There we go.
That works wonders.
Okay!
Are we done?
Let's see.
Look at that.
Where are we now?
You know what this looks like?
Oh, dude, this is like the magical temple.
And the reason...
I think this is supposed to be dark.
But I can see now.
Because all seeing eye.
It's the exact same layout as the...
or like enemies and brickwork and all that stuff.
As the magical temple.
So it's like a second magical temple of some sort.
Dude, I need to get some blood.
Cut this guy up.
Oh, but the blood spreads over such a large area.
It's useless.
Yeah, the audio is bogging again.
This run is already so successful, dude.
Holy crap.
Drink that.
By the way, speaking of eggs.
So I watched the intro cinematic again.
Before last stream.
Wait, what happened?
Oh, I'm confused.
And in that intro cinematic.
That egg was there.
And the egg cracked open.
And like air came out.
And my theory is that all the elements.
I think fire came out.
Water came out of it.
The different elements came out of the egg.
So something like that, I guess.
That's all I had to say there.
I have no other idea what's going on.
Also, there's something about a huge swallow or some kind of swan creature.
Oh, and tentacles came out of the egg too.
Tentacles came out of the egg.
Very weird stuff.
Also, I'm leaving behind all kinds of...
I should go back and refill this, I think.
There's a severe lack of blood here.
That is disappointing.
Whoa!
Oh, I blocked that?
Oh, there must have been an explosive effect on it, I guess.
Oh, I'm neutralized.
That is actually a wild debuff.
Now we're talking.
Give me that blood.
Where the hell am I?
It didn't say magical temple when I entered.
Actually, it didn't say anything, I don't think.
Unless it said it right when I activated the triangle and I didn't pay attention because all kinds of shit was happening.
I'm gonna be lazy here.
What?
My dude has black holes too!
I took a bunch of damage!
We're leaving.
Nope, we're leaving.
We got a heal.
Immediately.
This is way too crazy.
Thunder, I don't want that.
Do I want any of these, I wonder?
Wait, this is my old one, I think.
Oh, that's the egg wand.
Question, should I go up or down?
There is a heal up.
And that's confirmed heal.
Let's go up.
I have very low HP.
It is very risky what I'm doing.
Oh my god.
Chest, oh my god.
I can't tell where I've been and not been.
But I guess that's the point.
Don't!
Okay.
Okay, we're going down, we're going down.
We're not going up.
We got to play this safe.
Oh, it's the spider.
Okay, blood.
Now we're talking.
Why is that just stuck there?
Very odd.
Do I have healing here?
I do, I'm just going to take it.
I don't care.
Just take the healing and then we fill up the blood potion.
I don't think there's enough blood here anyway to heal me up fully.
What?
Oh!
This is the last stage.
Apparently there's lava underneath here.
All the way, huh?
Fuck off.
Oh, I didn't realize it.
Why am I taking damage?
What?
It just happened.
Weird.
Oh, no.
Oh, that sucks.
Dick!
Rip this wand.
I think this means the run is over.
I can't edit my wands anywhere.
I'm done.
This is what I'm left with for the rest of the game.
As far as I know, of course, as far as I know.
But I just don't see where else we could do anything.
It's fucking over.
That's rough, man.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
We can take this.
That's something we can do.
And...
I can...
Oh, I don't have enough money for this.
Oh, it doesn't matter anyway.
I can't use these spells.
It's rip.
My teleport wand.
Man, that sucks so much.
God damn it.
Why did I do that?
I'm an idiot.
Okay, let's just...
Okay.
New plan.
I'm gonna go up...
All the way to the top now.
And then we're just gonna wander the land.
Now that we have all seeing eyes, see what we can discover for the next run.
Basically.
Also, I'm gonna go back to the ancient laboratory and try and kick that fucking guy's ass.
Who's in there.
Who's gotten the best of me twice now.
Actually, that's not true.
He killed me once.
And the second time...
Uh, he disappeared for some reason.
So I don't know what that is all about, but...
Like, why is this guy so...
Insanely hard to kill.
He reflects the spells.
We gotta be quick with dodging, I guess.
So if I fall...
Oh, yeah, this is just...
It's over, man.
This is over.
Wait, is he even gonna do anything to me?
What if I stand still next to him?
Oh!
Interesting!
What if I kick you?
Huh.
Okay.
Well, okay.
I'm actually kind of glad I just tried that.
Now I feel them a lot less.
Just don't hit them with spells, I guess.
What about a black hole?
Do you like that?
You don't care about that, it seems.
Shit, I really need my teleport wand.
Hmm.
I guess what I could do is to just wander the land in search of a perfect wand.
Maybe I just happen to find a wand that is amazing.
Chances are pretty low, though.
It's there, though.
Chances are there.
Seal up here.
I use these like candy right now.
Oh, no.
Oh, don't hit that guy, don't hit that guy.
You wanna grab this blood, though?
I'm actually so happy I discovered I don't take damage from these guys.
That is also vital information for later.
Oh, oh!
I swear to god, electricity is the scariest thing in this game.
The fact that it stuns you is wild.
Drowning in slime here.
Okay, so we're at the top now.
Let's find our way to the actual...
That's the edge.
You know what?
How about we try to explore the western part of this place, now that we have all seeing eye.
I wanna see if there's any secrets there.
Or I could go back to where I just was.
I mean, that magical temple place.
Yeah, you know what?
Let's do that.
I actually kind of forgot about it.
I completely forgot about that.
Let's go back there.
I have changed my mind.
Look at all that slime.
Yikes.
Everything is destroyed here.
Let's see the bottom.
So the bottom is here.
I'm gonna walk along the outer edge.
Just to see the dimensions of this place.
And I need to update the map with this as well.
Actually kind of exciting.
Exciting stuff.
Okay, that's not very much blood.
Wax.
I can use this.
What the- Someone's invisible.
With a wand and a fiery wand.
Oh, he's protected now.
Oh, he's being buffed.
Look, he's inside the buffing region of his friend.
What's going on over here?
What an idiot.
Sir, are you all right?
Is he not totally killing himself?
It's an invisible guy with a wand who shoots.
What the- Oh, and there my game crashed.
Fuck.
Is everything corrupted now?
Oh, no.
Autosave found.
Should the game attempt to restore?
Let's do it.
Let's see if everything's fine.
It may just be ripped.
I mean, this run was fucked anyway.
Right.
Okay.
Wait, it actually set me back a little bit.
Maybe that's a good sign.
Maybe.
Oh, we gotta kill this buffer.
Also, this guy doesn't have a wand anymore now for some reason.
Yeah, look.
Buff gone.
I'm just gonna keep going.
Hopefully nothing broke.
We'll have to see.
The thing is, I don't know what this place is supposed to look like, so maybe things will be missing again and I won't even know.
Unless, sometimes it's quite obvious, I guess.
Like last time, it was, it felt off, you know what I mean?
You could feel something wasn't right.
I think he died.
Oh, he was shooting eggs everywhere.
This guy is poisoned.
Just drink all that blood.
Who shot that?
Dynamite.
We don't care about that.
We are immune to dynamite and all of its effects.
So that is like a poison mist, I guess.
It looks like blood mist, just green, right?
It's the same kind of spell.
Kill that dude.
Oh, there's so many invisible people here.
This all seeing eye is definitely not all seeing.
It's only partially seeing.
What an absolute scam.
Nuke orbit?
Calm down, dude.
A nuke orbit.
Jesus.
I wonder if that works with infinite spells.
I mean, that's ripped now because I can't get any more perks.
So this is what I got, man.
This is what I have to live with.
Kill this dude.
Okay, so there's a roof here.
So it does definitely look like some sort of...
Hold on, it goes up now.
I need to get the entire layout here.
Let's see.
I'm going to walk along the top here just to see.
Okay, so it stays like that.
Let me go.
Oh, I can make a hole through here.
It's no issue.
Don't you dare pick that up.
Let's make him more bloody.
I'm actually low on HP here.
This is bad.
These guys are doing some serious damage.
Okay, so it's just basically flat roof here.
I need to see the entrance again.
Whoa!
What the fuck is that?
Is that you?
Oh, yeah, it's definitely someone doing something.
I got him though.
Oh, the audio is bugging again.
Are we about to crash?
The hell?
Oh, firecrackers.
That's what did it.
I see.
Anti-gravity?
Apply some lifting force.
Okay.
All right.
Well, not interested in that.
And the roof is still kind of flat here.
I'm going to dig.
Dig, dig, dig, dig, dig.
It's better if I do this just quickly up and down.
Just wiggle it around.
Watch this.
We're going to wiggle this guy.
Wiggle, wiggle.
Oh, the wiggle is effective.
I need to wiggle more enemies here.
Okay.
So it comes in like that and it's...
Gotcha.
So hold on.
Where are we now?
We are in the...
No.
Wait.
No, we are in the art.
We are here, of course.
So that now does something funny here.
There's like an opening.
I'm going to make a square, sort of.
I'm just going to naively sort of do...
Something like that.
Hold on.
That's a bit too thick.
Do something like that.
Let's say...
There.
And then somewhere over here, it actually changes.
And it sort of goes up.
I don't know what happens on the right side there, but for now, we know that it goes up.
In fact, it goes something like...
Oops.
Remove that square.
It's like rocky cliffs going up like that, right?
Okay, let's leave it like that for now.
And fill it out as we go.
Okay.
Let's go all the way to the right.
See where it ends.
And then we're going to wiggle this guy.
Wiggle, wiggle!
No, I'm going to leave it.
Ah, I'm not!
Do they bleed blood?
I don't think they do.
They're ghosts.
Yeah.
Okay.
Fuck you then.
You are of no value to me.
Basically, what I need is a...
You know in Mad Max, Fury Road, they have the blood bag, the guy, strapped to the front of the car.
And he has an IV plugged in, just sucking blood from him all the time.
High octane blood.
That's what I need in this game.
I need my own blood bag.
I need to be hooked up.
Oh yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
Hand over your innards.
Oh no, the confusion.
Why am I confused?
Oh, it was something about eating ambiguous meat, I think.
Something like that.
It actually sort of goes down the bottom here.
Very interesting.
Okay.
Uh oh.
He's immune.
Maybe he gets out of range.
Yeah, diddling time.
Why is that guy...
Wait, does he have another guy?
Wait, are there two of them on top of each other?
Are they buffing each other?
That's some bullshit.
I do not approve.
Wizards then!
Oh!
That's my type of place!
I like that!
Wizards then!
Yo!
Can I aggro one of them over here?
Come here.
I need to get them separated.
Boing!
Come on, kick it.
Ball in his head!
My evil plan is working.
Oh, I'm neutralized!
Run!
Third?
What?
Oh, I'm twitchy now.
Okay, that's fine.
Neutralized and twitchy, so I occasionally do nothing.
What?
Did I hit teleportation?
I must have.
Oh my god.
Uh, look at this guy!
Look at his head!
Oh, I'm scared of that protection.
I'm scared of the projectile.
I'm scared of what it'll do.
Come here!
Wow, he has HP.
Got you.
I can't hit anything.
I'm terrible at aiming.
There we go.
Get the money.
Although, what am I going to use the money for?
Well, I guess there's still...
No, actually, I don't know what to use the money for anymore.
What?
Hey, who wants to get frozen?
You want some?
All right, fine.
What's this?
Random projectile?
No, thanks.
Wait, what's this?
Old brickwork.
How is this game bigger and bigger?
I almost can't believe there's this place here.
Like, what?
What?
This game is huge, and there's a wand in the brickwork!
Actually, there's a guy in there, too.
I think I killed him.
With healing on it.
Oh, but to do this, I need somehow to hit myself.
Hold on.
Does this fall down?
No.
Fuck, how did I do this last time?
Oh, but I can't edit my wands!
It's useless.
Hold on, there's another wand there.
Dumbass.
I'm drunk now.
Whoop!
Am I also...
Oh, that's why.
I'm erratic.
That's why I'm drunk.
Man, the spread is actually real when you're drunk.
Let's get some blood up in this.
I'm eating ambiguous meat.
Okay, not bad.
That was a lot of HP.
Cursed rock!
What?
Ethereal meat!
Still produces blood.
Weird.
Drink, drink, drink, drink, drink.
Okay, so, cursed rock at the bottom there.
Also, I have not paid attention to the layout here of the outside regions.
Man, all these enemies produce so much blood when you kill them.
Almost full HP.
Oh no.
We need to take care of the buffer.
You.
Nice.
This place is not that hard.
This is fine.
I'm okay.
Uh, invisible dude?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Be careful here.
Dormant crystal with trigger.
You know what?
I do want to try something.
Does this dig?
I guess a little bit.
Yeah.
Ah, I'm confused.
Get it off of me.
There we go.
Oh, no.
We got Ukus.
Oh, there are no problems.
Oh, he's being buffed.
No, he's not.
What's happening here?
Oh, it's you.
You were doing something.
A good old lightning bolt wand.
Look at that.
Oh, the intro.
Look at the banner.
It's the egg with the tentacles.
You see it?
Right there.
Also, by the way, the intro also had a huge emphasis on stars and the night sky.
I forgot to mention that, but...
Yeah.
Which actually ties in with the whole, like, everything has a counterpart thing we read about.
Remember?
Like dark matter?
Slimy egg.
Okay.
Oh, no.
There's these guys here.
Wait, what?
Stop shooting.
I need to get rid of this.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Water the lava.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Thank you, thank you.
Okay, hold on.
This place is nuts.
What?
Where am I now?
Uh-oh.
Don't hit this guy.
It's dangerous.
I need to see the layout.
No!
I ran out of levitation.
That was an almost huge disaster.
Holy crap.
I mini heart attack just now.
Okay, go back west.
Stop shooting me.
Give me this blood.
What?
I guess I must have touched the teleportation.
Dang it.
Really wish I had a teleport wand.
Okay, so where is the cursed rock?
Wait, what?
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm so confused by the layout right now.
Wait, what the...
I came from up here, no?
Did I...
Wait a minute.
Let's see.
Oh!
No, no!
That is the scariest.
Did I get you?
Guys, I am sweating profusely.
Sawblades, man.
That's something else.
Wait, no, no.
I didn't come from up here.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I came from down.
Okay, so this layout is very, very weird.
Let me keep going down here.
So we cursed rock here.
And if I keep going right,
I should be a way down.
Wait, what?
Oh, wait.
Did I teleport into some other area?
By accident?
Like with teleportation?
Is that why I don't know my way around here?
Is that what actually...
Did I get through a wall or something?
It's cursed rock everywhere.
How did I get in here?
What?
So this is like a completely different area I...
So did I get super lucky that I somehow came in here?
Because this seems like a completely separate area.
Like completely.
This is not the wizard's temple or whatever.
Or is it?
Oh no.
At least there's a lot of...
Jesus, look at that congregation up there.
This guy can fuck right off.
I need to drink, damn it.
I'm gonna lead him up here.
Also, I have a twitchy finger.
Let's lead him around.
By the way, all these enemies I see here, all I see is blood.
Potential blood.
I see why it's called the wizard's place.
There's only wizards!
Get the blood.
See, now he's scared.
He's scared of something over here.
And I'm not sure why he's scared.
Fill up the blood.
Are you scared over here as well?
You are not!
He...
He disappeared.
He disappeared after I destroyed that crystal.
He disappeared!
Was he scared of the crystal?
Ah!
Dude, you cannot get polymorphed in this game.
Getting polymorphed is actually the end.
Damn.
Okay.
But you know what?
This was a banger of a run.
Holy shit.
We figured out some stuff.
Also, I'm gonna put the death counter correct now.
74.
Okay.
That was a good run.
Honestly, I'm kind of relieved that it's over, just because we couldn't edit our ones anyway.
It was fucking over anyway.
There's nothing we could do.
We got all the perks we could have gotten.
It's over, you know?
So, I'm really glad I got to discover at least that extra part.
So, now I know I can get there later and get it potentially.
And see what's going on in there.
Yeah.
But I think...
Okay, here's my main thing I want to do in the game right now.
My main objective is to go to the ancient laboratory and fuck up that guy.
It's gotten personal at this point.
So, whatever I need to do that, I'm gonna find.
You know?
It's a bit of a chaotic want.
Is it better though?
Hard to say.
That's a dead end.
I keep wanting to eat the blood.
But now we're not vampires anymore.
Blood disgusts us.
Ew!
Blood?
Yikes.
We don't want that.
No way.
Last time, we were a bit of a butcher.
Sawing off everything we saw and consuming their innards and blood and all that.
This time, we are a civilized wizard.
Okay.
We have manners.
We do not engage with blood.
Or drink the innards of our enemies.
We are precise, calculated, and cold.
Nice.
Burn in hell, Huerta.
Oh shit, I'm also about to burn in hell.
Let's be careful.
In fact, I'm gonna wet myself so that I'm immune.
Also something I recently figured out, believe it or not.
Oh, I can get in there.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, he's dead.
Let's just leave him to it.
Leave him to his own devices.
Water everything.
Hold on.
I'm gonna try and shoot him with this.
Nah, it's not.
It's actually worse.
I almost got a shell to the face.
Oh, I thought you were stuck in there.
Little asshole.
I was planning my approach with you.
And then you surprised me.
Berserkium!
I do enjoy that.
In fact, I'm gonna consume half of that.
Just to make our shots better.
Okay, I've been up there.
Don't you even think about it?
Isn't this very open?
It seems very open.
The RNG here is very odd.
Okay.
Wait, what?
Oh, nevermind.
Thought I saw something.
Oh, wait, hold on.
Dude, I know what to do.
We need this, of course.
The ultimate.
Hey.
Dude, that was 1100 damage.
1100 at this time in the game.
Wait, where did they go?
Oh, I forgot to pick it up again.
Damn it.
I'm gonna use it on him.
Oh, that was close.
I'm on fire.
Oh, the gold.
That's sad.
Very...
Ooh, look at this.
I'm definitely getting in there.
Oh, no.
Yeah, that'll do.
Good enough for me.
Water ourselves and let's head out.
Don't get hit by the flames.
There's a wand as well.
Oh, he has a wand!
Oh, no.
Hey.
That's...
Come here.
I'm gonna drop this on his head.
Ah, fuck.
Oh, he shoots bombs, huh?
He just shot himself.
No!
We're fine.
This is the funniest duel ever.
Okay, man.
Well, he killed himself.
That's what I like to see.
Or did he go in the water actually?
And died.
I'm not sure.
Energy sphere.
That's what I'm talking about.
And it's a decent wand too.
Yo, that's sick.
That's a really good wand.
Fan-fucking-tastic.
Okay, let's go west.
Actually, let's just go where we haven't explored.
Black areas.
I can go up here.
Do you want to destroy that?
Hamis?
First Hamis I see today, I think.
We have to salute the Hamis.
It is his backyard after all.
The Hamis sphere.
Okay, I can get through here.
Dude, I picked up an empty wand.
Boo, throw it away.
Nice, HP!
Mmm, fantastic.
This is a great start so far.
I'm digging it.
Mmm, do I want to bomb that?
I don't think I will.
Gotta save it.
Also, when I find something I can destroy the cliffside with, I'm going to go up and grab the health on top of the mountain too.
That looks like a trap to me.
And it sure is.
Electrical trap.
I wonder if I have time to grab it and quickly get out.
Everything's going to get electrocuted.
I don't think I have time.
I'm going to use my bomb.
Oh no, I'm in a bad spot.
Oh, barely didn't get hit.
That was a bit lucky, honestly.
Huh.
I mean, maybe I should have just checked the wand first.
I don't even want it.
Oh, oh, oh.
Okay, there's one in there.
Toxic sludge is not a problem, but we can't get in, unfortunately.
Ah, wait, wait.
Yes, we can.
Watch this.
Oh, wait, no, wait.
We have multiple options.
I was going to have him aim at me down there and toxic my way through.
I would have been smart.
But this also works.
Okay.
That's actually not bad.
That digs.
I'll destroy this.
So many spark bolts.
This is not a bad wand either.
0.22, 0.38.
Wait, isn't this the exact same...
That is so...
Whoops.
Didn't mean to take it.
That is so weird.
Exact same stats again.
I've had this happen a lot recently.
The issue with this wand is that it produces a lot of toxic stuff.
Nobody really likes that stuff.
Thanks.
Very cool.
Come on.
What?
Okay, fine.
Be that way.
Oh, we're at the entrance now.
Pretty neat.
Dude, I'm gonna drain.
We're totally draining.
Okay, I thought he was on the right.
That's why it went up.
I was bamboozled there.
I was tumbled.
Let me go along the bottom here.
Clear out all the stragglers.
Dang it.
Whoops, I didn't mean to do that.
I thought I had the toxic wand on me.
Of course, I exchanged it.
I forgot.
Crap.
Well, we still have two.
How am I so bad at aiming?
That was like that.
Have you seen Hot Shots Part 2?
There's this really funny scene with an archer trying to hit someone and he keeps like ducking and just doing things all the time and he's shot like 20 arrows and misses all of them.
It's exactly like that.
Man, that is such a funny movie.
I gotta watch that again.
It's been a while.
Charlie Sheen in his prime.
Okay,
I'm gonna go here.
Oh, something in there.
Water.
I mean, I'll take it.
Thanks.
It's nice to have some extra water.
Uh, shit.
It is kind of annoying that I can't dig like small scale.
How am I gonna get through here?
Like this?
Oh yeah, that works.
Don't even think about it.
This has been going swimmingly.
That is exactly what I need.
No, but wait.
That doesn't work in there, does it?
In the cave.
Oh no.
Shit.
What?
Look at how good this weapon is against the frogs.
Did I check this one?
I did.
Did I have any bombs left on it?
I did not.
Okay, so it's useless.
I need to start using this liberally.
These guys always get a hidden on me somehow.
It's like my brain can't compute how to dodge their projectiles.
They're way too awkward, they're way too slow, and their rate of fire is just always messing with my mind.
It's just so annoying.
Nice.
Water everything.
Oh, we've got a dude in there.
We've got a rainmaker.
That's what I'm going to call him now.
Rainman.
That's a good word.
Hey, Rainman.
Do you like toxic waste?
Oh wait, I have this.
What?
Was that not point blank?
Oh my god.
Hey, dude.
I can't...
Do not die now.
Oh!
Jesus!
Fuck.
What an annoying piece of shit.
How much HP do you have?
And where did you get all that?
Asking for a friend.
I'm totally oily now as well.
Oh my lord.
Give me your money.
And give me that tablet.
That's an annoying enemy.
Very difficult enemy in the early game.
So I'm almost out of health here.
It's kind of problematic.
Worta in my way.
Okay.
Percircium.
I will take it.
Switch these out.
In fact, drinks.
I should have drunk that for fighting that dude just now.
I didn't think.
Oh, no.
Okay, so this does not work.
Unfortunately.
But we do have a black hole.
So we can drain.
Drain the water completely and I can wander in the dark.
I mean, the big issue is drowning.
So if I can not drown, everything's fine.
Okay, this is actually perfect.
Look, it's amazing.
And then we're gonna...
I'm gonna do this.
Oh, that's a slow ass black hole.
The hell...
What the fuck was that?
That's better.
Drain it up.
Now, can I see it?
I could find a worm, I guess.
But that is a bit too risky with my HP.
That is not happening.
No way.
I may also just...
Oh, I used all of my black holes, of course.
Question is, is this gonna be enough to drain it all?
Maybe it is.
It's draining rather slowly.
I'm too terrified.
What if there's enemies in there?
Okay.
I think it's a bad idea.
Don't go in there if you don't have any way to see.
Even if it's drained, it's just...
It's a recipe for disaster.
I'm gonna go through here now.
Let's go.
It's fine.
I can heal here.
And let's see what we have.
Okay.
Poland, that's digging.
That's digging.
And okay.
What's this?
Uh, breathless.
You can no longer drown.
That would have been nice to have, like, one minute ago.
Hmm.
I'm not sure I like it.
This seems completely useless.
Like, let's say there's another wand.
Whoop-de-fucking-do another useless wand.
Like, wow.
Boomerang spells.
No.
Oh.
Your spells arc toward you, but gain extra.
That would be nice for healing stuff.
Telekinetic kick.
Hmm.
That is tempting.
But I am gonna do one more.
God damn it.
This is all crap.
Maybe I'll take this.
You inflict more damage, the more satiated you are.
Let's try this.
I'm gonna have an open mind here.
Fuck it.
We're experimenting.
So, hold on.
I am at 74% satiation.
How much more are we talking?
This does five damage.
Hey, that...
That's not bad.
That's almost double.
Actually, it is double.
It's more than double.
What's this?
It's...
Hardy...
Porridge potion?
What?
I got some food with it?
No way.
Hold on.
You're actually kidding.
100% Hardy Porridge?
Huh.
Okay.
I think...
Oh, I don't have any money for it.
Oh, I have money for this one.
I may just get it.
The digging is actually wild with the...
The pollen digging is real.
I'm taking it.
Now, the one itself is kind of...
Not the greatest.
But it's fine for pollen, I guess.
Not bad, huh?
Not bad at all.
Although this one is even better, I think.
Oh, yeah.
Maybe.
Actually, I'm not sure.
Whoa.
No!
Ah, whatever.
Didn't think about that.
Whoops.
I mean, this is fine.
Then we have these guys right here.
So, if this does three damage now...
So, I'm at 40% satiation.
Wait.
You inflict more damage the more satiated you are, but you start losing.
All right.
I start losing health if I don't have any.
Oh, that's actually not the greatest.
It's fine.
We're experimenting.
Let's put this up here.
I don't want any of that.
This is my digger.
Except I think I like the digging in this more.
Let's do that.
And then these ones can stay.
Although, maybe I should keep this one just because it's non-shuffle, and then I can throw this one away.
Yeah, that makes more sense to me.
Let's do it like that.
Okay, let's move on.
Let me eat some of this hardy porridge.
Wait, what?
It healed me.
Hold on a second.
I thought it was just be like a potion.
Oh, here's some food so you can satiate yourself.
I was wrong.
Hold on.
Poland does not dig through this, right?
It does not.
Okay.
Cold pits.
Hardy porridge.
Now I'm starting to think.
What?
Already?
What do you mean?
What do I need to eat?
Cannot drink water?
What do I eat?
Greeny slimy meat.
Can I eat that?
Oh, that's bad.
I'm puging now.
Oh, fuck me.
This is holy shit though.
I eat the porridge.
I don't know what to eat.
I need to eat blood.
Oh, I'm out of water now too.
Oh, this is a complete disaster.
This is actually the worst.
Oh my fucking god.
It's ore.
No water anywhere in sight.
This guy.
I will eat you.
I ate him.
Yeah, we gained a bit of satiation.
Why am I poisoned?
I didn't touch anything just now.
I'm so confused.
Uh, go here.
You, I'm gonna eat you.
My screen is...
It's shaking a lot for some reason.
Eat, eat, eat, eat, eat.
Yes.
Oh yeah.
Eat a lot.
Okay, I ate those guys.
Great success.
Oh yeah, the blood is good.
Blood is good.
Keep eating blood.
Yes.
Okay, we're back in action.
I was panning a little bit there.
I never actually questioned why I would sometimes gain satiation and what I was eating to gain it.
But I guess it's just meat.
And blood.
Can I eat plants?
No.
You cannot.
I'm puking a lot here.
Oh, that's nice.
Thanks.
I like this one too.
This, this one is actually insane.
Right here?
Hmm,
we got to eat some more porridge.
I feel like I've wasted a lot of this porridge, but it is what it is.
Now I know that that's the thing.
So by the way, regarding the porridge.
Now I'm starting to think, can I somehow make my own porridge?
You know, it's a material that is in a flask.
Maybe if I mix the right ingredients, I can make it.
So wait, hold on.
Let's think about this porridge is water and wheat.
Pretty much.
Right?
Porridge and water and wheat.
That's all it is and some heat.
Wheat.
What is the closest thing to wheat is bread.
Do we have any bread in this game?
Can I actually fucking make porridge in this game?
If I can make porridge in this game, this is incredible.
I doubt.
Okay.
You got fucked there.
Don't you shoot me with that.
Where do you come from?
Where's your mom?
I know she's here somewhere.
They're getting spawned.
Oh my God.
It's not going well.
Oh, I need to keep eating.
I hate being.
I hate having to eat.
That does not please me.
I'm very unhappy with the eating.
This is like an unnecessary restriction to put on.
Like it's already not that great of a perk even without it taking damage.
Is it?
I don't know.
It just feels weird.
What what what?
Oh, I'm low.
Find some food.
I feel like killing myself, guys.
This is like, I feel like actually just ending it here.
I hate this perk so much.
It's actually the worst.
Eat these.
Like, it's not even allowed.
You get I get like 2% per rat.
We had a good run.
It's over.
Take me to the new one.
Yep.
I can't live with this.
That's simply the worst.
Take me up here now.
Eh, can I can I?
What?
Why does that not produce a hole?
Okay, not bad, not bad.
So these do a little digging.
It's not a lot.
So it's going to take a couple tries here.
But I will get it.
What?
That bounce off.
God damn it.
Okay, there we go.
There we go.
I basically can't hit it at an angle.
It needs to be straight on.
Otherwise it will bounce.
Yes, lovely stuff.
Solid start there.
Whoop.
Let's go this way.
I am tempted to just fight the worm immediately.
You know what?
I do have a lot of damage here.
I'm going to do it.
Because I want...
Not snow.
I want...
Oh, but hold on.
We would need something to slice up the meat.
Probably it's fine.
We will have enough.
You know what?
Maybe it's better to come back here when we have a reason to...
No, I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do it.
I have confidence.
We can do it this time.
I'm going to kick his ass.
Also, I have to remind myself what exactly was in there.
I can look at the map.
Of course.
That's why I made it.
What was in here?
Oh, a tablet, right.
Okay.
Not what I want.
In fact, I have an idea.
What if I release this next to an explosive?
Make my life easy.
Oh, but the issue is, I can't do it too far down, because if the worm accidentally angers the gods, that would be kind of a problem.
Yeah.
Maybe I'll do it right here.
And then I'm going to shoot it with the fire stuff I have.
I think it'll be enough.
Let's see.
There it is!
Awesome.
Now I have worm here.
I can always cut it up.
Beautiful.
Very nice.
That went really well.
It smells like soil after rain.
Look at these guys.
This is how new parts are made.
Oh,
no.
It's growing plants everywhere.
That's what that means.
Oh, that's horrible.
So, okay, there's a chance to have a modifier on these levels.
On every level, I guess.
Remember that one time we were in the coal pits, and we got the modifier that gave us...
Why is this so crooked?
It gave us like a shit ton of gold in the level.
Like, you smell riches in here or something, you know?
I want more of that stuff.
Ugh, the whiskey has been contaminated.
Bad.
Come on.
Why is that not digging?
Oh, flamoxium potion.
No, thanks.
That's what I'm talking about.
Nice consolation prize there.
Actually, I'm gonna get that wand.
It does involve getting a little drunk.
But I think that's a price worth paying.
Circle of shielding.
That is the one that just absorbs projectiles, I think.
We actually got to replace the snow with water.
Speaking of water, I got some right here.
Let's make a nice little snowman first.
How am I gonna get there easily?
I could drain.
Maybe this is enough.
If it burns away, I can get in there.
It'll take a while.
Oh wait, I have this.
Oh yeah, much better.
Beautiful.
Okay.
No.
Don't give me that poison.
Oh, yikes.
Did he die from drowning?
No way.
Oh no, I'm also dying.
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
Just kidding.
Nothing there, huh?
Holy shit, it's Friday.
I don't know why.
I've been thinking it was a weekday.
All this time.
I mean, it's taking me a weekday.
But you know what I mean?
I just remembered it's Friday.
Oh, that filled me with happiness.
Holy shit.
It just hit me.
What do we got here?
Nothing.
Wow.
That looked like a wand.
Man, I have to go all the way around?
That sucks.
Okay, I'm watered up.
I'm okay.
And I'm immune.
Got to cut my way through this jungle here.
I don't like that the jungle has invaded my hemisphere.
In fact, it makes me very displeased with the situation.
On the bright side, maybe all this poison will kill any potential enemies down there.
Oh, the water, it comes to clean it up.
This is not great.
This is all locked off.
Give me bombs.
Give me black holes.
Give me anything I can dig.
I haven't found one of those plasma cutters in ages.
Like, when am I going to find that again?
From now on, I'm going to really appreciate them when I find them.
No, don't grow that shit.
Thank you.
209.
Decent.
Let's get that guy trapped with the plants.
And now I'm trapped.
Wow.
Oh, wait, I'm not trapped.
It's fine.
Very surprised I haven't seen any of the fire dudes yet.
Uh-oh.
Look at that.
Stop that growth.
Oh, man.
You're fucking up the distillery.
What is this?
Get out of here.
We need to brew.
Jesse, we need to brew.
I'm stuck in here now.
This is unreal.
Burn the shit.
In fact, grab this thing.
It's too dangerous to have lying around.
I can't get out of here.
Okay, where's the oil?
Show me the oil.
There's some here.
That's not enough.
Look at that.
The portal is covered in growth.
Isn't that a beautiful sight, actually?
I enjoy that.
Gotta find some oil.
Dammit, dead end.
There's the fire dude.
Now I can't enter here.
That's unreal.
Feel an invisible force pushing you around?
Hold on.
Now I'm too curious.
The hell does that mean?
I gotta get through here.
Oh, this one is way better.
What the hell?
Can I kick it?
Oh, I can't get through there.
Or maybe I can...
If I burn this, I can't get through anyway.
Fuck me, I can't go there.
Wand up there.
Maybe I can sneak around and get it from this angle.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, sir!
That's what I need, baby.
Yes!
Will it take care of these things too?
Oh, that's lovely.
I think at least.
Is it actually or...
Oh, that's burning.
That's nice.
Water me up.
Nice and wet.
And then we go.
We have gained access.
If I destroy this in time, will it stop growing?
I wonder.
As soon as I see another one, I'm gonna try and shoot it immediately.
Someone has a shield here of some sort.
Okay, there's a dude there that needs attention.
Oh, interesting.
Weird.
And this is pulling in?
Oh, yeah!
That's fucking awesome!
Look at that!
How cool is that?
Oh, no!
What?
Oh, he hit me with dynamite.
That is so funny.
That's a funny mechanic.
Uh-oh.
Let's not bag ourselves into a corner here.
Whoa!
That was a fantastic shot there.
Oh, he died.
Good.
I think it may be time for us to peace out.
20 HP.
That's not a lot.
Kind of want to get that want, though.
Can I dig through this?
I cannot.
Rock is a no bueno.
But...
Uh-oh.
Oh, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hey, fuck it.
Maybe use...
I'll just do this.
Yes!
Dude, this is great!
Hell yeah!
That worked wonders!
How can I get in there?
Somehow.
Maybe here.
Through the...
Nope.
I think that want is off limits for me, unfortunately.
That's unfortunate.
Maybe there's something over here so I can dig?
No.
Oh, that was close.
What's going on with this boulder?
I am doing this risk...
It's risky what I'm doing here.
It really is.
Okay, that worked.
Lovely stuff.
Yo, totally worth it to explore.
Really funny how there's a...
Heart right next to the portal, huh?
Tell me I can get in there.
Shit.
There's rock.
I can't.
That was almost very close.
No, it was very close.
Not almost.
I know I'm squeezing the lime here, people.
I am.
The lemon is being squeezed.
Maybe a bit too hard.
Got some more water.
I have no means of seeing.
Playing this very slow right now.
Okay.
Is this body being pulled in?
That's funny.
Okay.
The roots are blocking my way.
I think that's it.
We gotta go.
That was nice.
Not a lot of money though.
Wow.
I'm very surprised at the lack of money there.
Nice.
And some light.
What do we got here?
Dammit.
Gain two random perks at this point?
Sure.
Fuck this game, man.
Unreal.
Give me that.
And that.
Um, I'm gonna...
What am I gonna do?
Is this good?
Hold on.
Let's see.
Point zero five?
No, that sucks.
Wait, why is that so bad?
What?
Is that bugged?
That's...
Look at the top right.
Look at the bar.
It's all like wiggly and fucked.
Yeah, that's bugged as hell.
Or not bugged, but it's definitely weird looking.
Very odd.
Uh, energy sphere with timer?
What else do I want?
Maybe a bit of light.
Uh, I think that's it.
Maybe this one for later.
This is fine, I think.
Not bad.
But...
Okay, so technically...
Oh, hardy port.
There we go.
I should be able to do this.
Question is, can I defeat the guy coming out now, though?
Uh, I feel...
Okay, I'm gonna take my chances just because I have this shit perk anyway and I feel like taking my own life anyway.
So we're gonna be digging.
Here he comes.
Oh yeah, he's already angry.
Maybe he doesn't like this stuff.
Oh, it bounces right off.
Ah, shit, I picked it up by accident.
Okay, I have an idea, I have an idea.
Yes!
Okay.
Now if he comes close, maybe that thing will hit him.
Come here.
That's right, stand right there.
Why am I taking damage?
No!
It doesn't, it doesn't...
Oh, it only lasts for a certain amount of projectiles, I think.
It's not time-based, it's projectile-based.
Oh no.
We're gonna be hot swapping right now.
Okay, he's sort of stuck.
Maybe.
Did I hurt him at all?
Come on.
I don't think that's doing anything to him at all.
I can't kill him, I can't kill him.
Why am I taking damage?
Oh, yeah, just kill me.
I don't give a fuck.
I hate this perk.
What a terrible perk.
Holy shit.
It's like the worst perk in the entire game.
Like...
I mean, that I can see right now.
It's not even a benefit, it's to your detriment.
It's that bad.
Like, I would rather not have any perks than have that.
You know?
Unless you can find some kind of perk in combination with it that will somehow eliminate the shitty part of that perk, then maybe it's good.
But until then, damn.
That was unlucky, man, getting that perk.
Really unlucky.
And it was such a good run too.
You know, I had such good amounts of hearts and stuff.
It was a really nice hemisphere.
But oh well.
And is this snow again?
It is, okay.
So here's what we can do.
We can fill this up with snow, make it water, and then we have a water potion.
Smart, huh?
Let me make a mountain of snow here.
Nice and big.
And we get the water.
Does this guy have a...
He's dual wielding a wand and a shotgun.
I need to teach that guy a little thing or two.
If I can even get in there, I can't probably.
I do have three bombs.
I can definitely get in from upstairs.
Oh yeah, he's mine.
You're mine, baby.
What kind of wand do you have?
Circle of stillness.
That's a really good one.
Very nice.
Good start, good start.
I love me some circle of stillness.
I only recently discovered how good that is.
Okay, dead end.
Don't waste bombs.
Don't do it.
Maybe I should start trying or stop trying to be so systematic with the exploration, even though it may not look systematic.
I am actually trying.
Maybe it's better if I just go wherever the wind takes me.
Fuck it, let's just go.
I'm just gonna wander.
Man, lack of enemies, huh?
This is the worst.
When you discover one of these paths, you go all the way to the end.
And it doesn't connect to anything.
You have to go all the way back.
Oh, here we go, here we go.
Come here, bitch.
No!
Yes!
God, that feels good.
Yes, sir.
The old kick to the face.
Get rid of the toxic.
Sweet.
I'm in maximum focus mode now.
Come here.
Weird fungus pouch.
Oh, we're getting high.
Oh, it's time, baby.
Fuck you.
Don't destroy the pouch!
No, don't burn it, don't burn it.
Don't burn the drugs.
All right.
Let's forget about our troubles for a moment.
And have a snack, shall we?
I was about to say, will it grow on wood?
But it will, I think.
No!
Don't you ruin my day.
I'm about to have a wild time in here.
It's gonna be good.
Oh, yeah.
Look at that.
Is that enough?
Oh, yeah, let's see.
We're gambling.
Come on.
Make a nice mountain.
There we go.
Okay, eat it all.
Just keep eating.
Five hundred seconds.
What?
Poison?
Oh, no.
What became poison?
Wait, what?
Wait, wait, wait.
What, what, what, what?
What became...
I'm so confused.
I have four HP.
I'm not sure what happened.
Look at the Hamis family.
Oh, man.
Something that was in this pouch became...
Wait.
Coal, grass, soil, and poison transformed.
It's got to be the fungus itself?
Did the fungus become poison?
I have fungus in that pouch, no?
Or no, I emptied the pouch completely, and then I must have walked over something and picked...
That's a nice collection of vomit there.
I guess I'll notice when I walk around, maybe.
Exactly what's going on, but...
That sure does not look good, does it?
I may have to go through right now.
Four HP?
We can't work with that.
No way.
Okay, what's this?
No.
Wait, hold on.
I'm not sure what that is.
Digging?
Egging?
And triplicating.
What is that?
Oh, do I really want a vampirism again?
I feel like I've had enough of blood.
It's a bit too much.
Let's, let's, uh, do this.
Hey.
That's nice.
That's a good one.
Okay, now with the remaining money, we can't buy shit, so it's time to move on.
There's literally nothing we can do.
So, just go.
I need to find a way to leave the holy mountain without angering the gods.
And without having, uh, yeah, basically without angering the gods.
I mean, if I don't find the long distance teleport.
That's what I mean.
Because that is the one way I know.
If I can only figure that out.
Are those fish?
Wait, what is that?
Look at that!
There's gold floating in the water?
Empty that.
I'm curious to see what exactly...
No, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, wait, wait, wait.
When this has poison, that means something else.
That that means poison changed into something.
Right?
And not that something changed into poison.
Although, I...
Man, I can never remember that.
You know how some people have trouble distinguishing left and right, which I've never had an issue with.
But some people apparently do.
I have the same issue with the...
With that message.
And I cannot, for the life of me, remember what it actually means.
What got shifted?
Okay, get the money.
Good.
Now we need to find a bunch of hearts.
This is actually big.
Finding that perk in the first holy mountain is actually huge.
Especially because we didn't really explore the first place, right?
So there's potentially a bunch of hearts there too.
I need to focus here.
Get rid of that guy.
There's a mom nearby, I think.
Okay.
Let's water these corpses.
Actually, no.
There doesn't have to be a mom nearby.
It's just, sometimes there is.
No want.
Ow!
A bit of fucking lava dripped on me there.
It's like when you're making soup and it boils, you know?
And it just spritzes on you sometimes and it gives you a burn.
That's what that felt like.
Oh no, it's the fungal cavern.
But guys, you know what that means.
We gotta get high again.
Maybe we can undo whatever just happened.
Uh-oh.
We've got the froggies.
Oh, they're actually the worst.
I have no spells that can probably deal with them.
Oh, fuck off.
Why is everything shaking?
Oh, fireworks are going off.
I get it.
Yep.
Grab that.
Water this bullshit.
Oh yeah, I'm definitely going in here.
Believe you and me.
36 HP and a dream.
No, wait.
We're playing safe.
I was focusing.
We're not doing that.
Make a bomb.
I heard a shotgun.
I'm scared of...
Tactical pause.
Sick.
He may be a shotgunner, but I'm a sniper.
Lovely stuff.
That's double.
I think so.
They give like 25 normally.
Now it gives 50, right?
No, wait.
How do I have 160 then?
Oh, because I get 10 when I finish a holy mountain.
That's right.
It all adds up, baby.
The math checks out.
What's that?
It's a pixel of something.
Can't tell.
I think it's blood, actually.
Hold on, there's a wand.
I am too curious.
Am I, though, that curious to go through toxic rock?
Yes, I am.
Are you there?
What are you doing?
Let's not touch anything.
Sweet.
That's not bad.
All right, now we leave.
Now we play it safe.
This one wasn't actually bad.
I do like the red glimmer.
And my bombs are gone anyway, so let's take it.
Yo!
Okay.
Let's make a lot of water.
There we go.
I can fix itself.
Man, I can't get through anywhere here.
I need to go all the way around.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Here we go.
These guys kind of look like something out of a...
Bomberman.
Don't they?
The way they hold the bombs and stuff?
They don't feel like any of the other characters.
They're very out of place, in a way.
But still in place, if that makes sense.
Unusual, I would say.
I'm gonna go along here and then down there.
Not many enemies.
Shotgun dude.
Nice.
Oh my god.
16 HP.
Not looking good.
Is that a Barney or a...
Yeah, that's a...
No, he has a mask on.
There we go.
Play it safe.
Let's just find out where the portal is.
Yeah, burn.
Does he even take damage from fire?
Doesn't look like it.
Let's not hit that way right now.
Too much fire.
Don't want to go here though.
Want to find more hearts.
This is the time to find hearts.
Of all the times.
Oh!
Absolute asshole down there.
I think I got him.
Portal.
I'm tempted to take it.
I think I'm gonna take it.
I have not explored very much in either the hemisphere or the coal pits.
Not very optimal.
But you gotta do what you gotta do.
Oh, would you look at that.
That's a laser cutter.
Oh, but hold on.
Can I fight the dude?
Oh, I don't think so.
I just want one of each of these.
Put them up here.
Let's see what ones I have.
Okay, so shuffle, non-shuffle.
This is a decent want.
That's not bad at all.
Oh, let's see the perks.
Contact damage.
Uh, enemy's near you take damage.
The damage is higher the lower your health gets.
No, I don't want that.
No longer drown.
Yeah, right.
Fungal creatures spawn from the corpses of enemies.
You know what?
Let's try it.
No, hold on.
What do you mean fungal creatures?
Fungal enemy creatures or fungal creatures on my side?
It's got to be on my side.
Otherwise, how is this a perk?
How is this a perk?
Oh, but enemies may drop blood money.
What does that even mean?
Fungal creatures.
This is the worst perk in the game.
Like, ones cannot be tinkered with ever?
How are you going to do anything in the game?
That doesn't make any sense to me.
Fucking hell.
These should not be called perks.
They should be called changes.
That makes me question whether or not this is actually going to spawn friendlies or not.
Let's try it.
Maybe friendlies will spawn.
I'm betting on it.
But who knows?
It's an experiment.
Let's see what this does.
Yo.
Yo, that's not bad.
That is really not bad.
Decent there.
And we have this guy.
That shoots four spells at the same time, but has a very low mana charge.
Could be like a shotgun.
Like ultra close.
Oh my god, that's terrible.
The recharge is horrible.
What is this?
Oh, reduces cast delay.
Wait a minute.
Dum, dum, dum, dum, dum, dum, dum.
Interesting.
This does five.
This does...
Yo, this is better.
This is better.
Spirit bolt is better.
I like that.
And then we have circle of stillness.
Can go there.
And that's pretty much it.
You can put some light on it, I guess.
Why not?
Just for fun.
And I think I'm good.
We are out of money.
Completely.
So I know there's a laser cutter here.
I need to remember that.
There's a laser cutter in the...
What is it then?
So it wasn't cold pits.
I guess next place is easy base?
No, it's this place first.
Right, snowy depths.
Right, okay.
Oh, look!
There they are.
Are you a friendly?
Whoa, I don't know if I like that.
They explode?
I don't know about that.
Um, I get through here.
Whoop!
Little backstabbing team here.
Look, they spawn.
Are you an enemy?
You're not!
Okay, thank God.
That's something.
And you explode, huh?
I can't damage you.
Okay.
Very cool.
Let's just see how much damage they do to enemies.
That's what I'm really doing.
True is about.
The fact that they explode makes me a little uneasy.
Look at that snowman.
Toxic sludge above each armpit.
Yo, look at the glue gang.
Oh, I see poison.
Where's that poison coming from?
Oh yeah, stuff is definitely poison here.
Something has changed into poison.
There we go.
Hey, it actually killed the enemy for me.
Sweet.
Okay, maybe these fungal guys are not too bad.
I do kind of want to eat them and get high.
Hey, fool.
Oh, he wasn't too bad at all.
Okay, I just saw another explosion.
Was that one of mine?
Doop.
So far, I think I kind of like the fungal guys.
I see a heart in there.
The hearts are extra valuable for us.
Oh God.
Nice.
Oh yeah.
What's up, guys?
Follow me.
We have places to explore.
Okay, so they explode in poison gas.
So the question is, have they always done that?
Or have they explored into something else in the past?
I have no idea.
Oh, hold on.
Oh, nice.
Well done, my little friends.
I love these guys.
They're my friends.
I want...
Can I get it though?
I don't really have any digging capabilities.
Hmm.
If I try hard enough, maybe it'll work?
What am I hearing?
Is that an Uco?
Let me in!
Oh, I'm out of mana, wow.
Oh man.
Don't...
I...
Don't do this at home.
This is terrible.
Don't ever dig with this thing.
I'll tell you, it's terrible.
But it works.
Um, yeah, definitely replace it.
Sure, why not?
One I have right there sucks.
So that's fine.
Let's go fuck up that guy.
Can I really not make you explode on command?
That would be great though, if I could.
Can use you as digging...
thingies.
It's dynamite, basically.
All right, Uco, where are you?
Show thyself.
Oh, I guess he died.
Now I'm gonna go down.
Nope, I lied.
I didn't lie.
I was truthful.
Wait, do they always spawn or just sometimes?
Oh, fungal creatures spawn from the corpses.
So all of them it seems.
And then they explode, that's lovely.
What do we have here?
Orbiting arc.
Wait, orbiting arc?
I have... I'm scared of this.
This scares me.
I'm not sure if I want to try that.
Let's not try this.
We can try that later.
When we're in a safe spot.
Wow, what an open place here.
Hello!
How's it going, bro?
Please die.
You cannot anger the gods, trust me.
I will be very unhappy if we do that.
In fact, I will be so angry with you.
Can I even...
I wonder if a fungal guy is gonna spawn out of this dude.
Oh no.
No, don't you go down there.
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no.
Run!
Please kill him.
Kill him!
Murder him!
That was close.
Goddamn!
All right, we're gonna drink all this.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah.
Eat it, eat it, eat it.
Oh, worm blood in my tummy.
Makes my nose runny.
500 seconds of worm blood, baby.
That is lovely, isn't it?
Uh-oh.
I should probably hit on.
You know, I shouldn't continue.
Yeah, I'm gonna go.
Yep.
Rip the laser cutter.
Now, what is that?
Heavy shot.
Interesting.
And then we have...
Close call.
Freeze field.
Hmm.
Glass cannon.
Spells are five times as powerful.
Yeah, how about no?
Maybe I'll take this.
Yeah.
You gain additional chance to deal critical hits as long as their enemy's near you, which is pretty much all the time.
There's always enemies near me in this game.
When is...
Are there not enemies near me?
Matter eater.
I will take this.
What's that?
Chaotic transmutation.
Am I hearing a worm?
No, I'm hearing explosions.
Also, look at this crazy shit.
I can see everything.
I can spy on everyone.
Oil cloud.
What's this?
Let's see.
Greatly increases the damage done by a projectile at the cost of its speed.
Oh, that is indeed a lot of damage.
Holy crap.
How fast is it now?
Oh, yikes.
Oh, that's terrible.
Uh, hold on.
Wait, how is that not a laser cutter?
It's almost exactly the same.
So this is gonna do a lot of damage, right?
I'm not entirely sure how that works.
In fact, that...
Okay, this thing killed me, remember?
Someone picked up my wand and killed me with this spell.
It actually did a lot of damage to me really quickly, too.
And as long as I was standing in the field, I got fucked.
You know, so...
Could be cool, I guess.
But even cooler is to put this maybe like that.
Is that cool, though?
I feel like that would sometimes hit me in the face.
Can I take damage from it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just wanted to make sure.
Uh, just wanted to make sure.
Good.
Now that I know that.
Uh, I do wish, I wish, I knew if the heavy shot did in fact...
affect the plasma.
I mean, of course it should.
Why shouldn't it?
I don't really know what else I can do here.
Makes a projectile separate into a bundle of five explosive bolts as soon as it moves downwards.
Which is pretty much immediately when you have heavy shot.
I need speed up.
Then this would be kind of crazy.
Speed up would be really nice.
A double.
What does this mana cost?
60?
What if I were to do... hold on.
400?
Oh, this always casts this arc thingy.
I need to experiment with that.
If I use this...
Oh, that's weird.
That's weird.
Why would you do that?
Oh, actually.
No.
If... oh, dude, if I had homing on this...
Homing would be crazy.
Homing... I just don't have enough money.
I'm tempted to just use my... try the plasma beam.
Just go plasma beam style.
I mean, it sounds cool.
Why not?
Why shouldn't I go plasma beam?
And then I could go like... this... with that on it... down here... just for the lulz.
Oh, wait, no, no, no, not this one, not this one, not this one.
Oh.
Oh, there's not enough mana?
Oh, wow.
Oh, that sucks.
Never mind.
I'm not going to use that.
Nope.
There we go.
All right, let's go.
All right, easy base.
Let's go.
Let's try this.
Oh, it does not cut through anything, so I gotta...
Ooh.
Wait.
No.
Wait, is it turning...
Is meat poison?
Hold on a second.
No way.
Oh, wait, this weapon is not that great.
And it does seem like the heavy shot is not actually affecting it.
At all.
This does not add 44 damage.
Look.
Wait, how did that guy die so fast?
It does 20.
Heavy shot does nothing there.
Damn, man.
Wait, is the blood...
Wait, is the meat actually become poison?
Oh, or is it blood?
No, because there's blood here.
Hold on, what else comes out of people?
I don't know.
I have no clue what got transformed into poison.
Blood, like look, none of this is poison.
If I cut it up...
What?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I think I understand now.
When they die, the fungal creatures spawn, and then they instantly explode, and that's where the poison comes from.
You know what?
This plasma thing is not half bad.
Like it definitely has its use here.
I can see it.
I can see it, dude.
Has a good range too.
It's not bad.
The fact that you can create like a perimeter, and nothing can move through it is kind of sick.
You can sort of block off an area like this, and when enemies go through, they just get shot, you know?
Pretty dope.
Oh, I'm poisoned again.
I like this weapon.
It makes me happy.
That's all that matters.
Doink!
Whoops.
Doink.
Like that's insanely effective.
I was tempted to just run into the fire there, because I have fire immunity, but I don't!
Some habits die hard.
Wait a minute, friendos!
We need to find pheromone.
This weapon is definitely something you gotta get used to.
It's very hard to fight with properly.
Oh, I'm poisoned again.
I just hit myself with the weapon, I think.
Again.
Whoa!
Be careful.
Oh my god, I'm getting bounced around left and right.
Not a good time right now.
Oh, yeah.
That's doing great.
My health is not looking very great, though.
Gotta wand.
That thing's gonna explode up there.
Aww!
I don't know why I played like this.
This was terrible.
I played very bad.
There's not much to say there.
I was in a bad spot.
I was paralyzed.
Well, not in game, but as a person trying to control this character, my hand was paralyzed.
I was scared!
I messed it up.
That's that.
That's too bad, man.
That would have been a crazy run with the extra HP from the hearts, though.
I never could figure out what the hell became poison, but whatever.
I didn't like the poison, so maybe that's for the best.
Like, whatever it was, doesn't matter, right?
Poison is bad.
Back in the hemisphere.
What's up, people?
I bet all the enemies here are just like, man, you're back here again?
Why are you here all the time?
I'm just here, okay?
Nice.
That is the most satisfying way to kill someone.
Just launch a barrel into their face.
No!
Man, acceleration is nice for just scoping out the environment.
Fuck you.
He tried to cut me with his knife just there.
You saw that?
Tried.
There's a wand.
Someone killed himself with it.
Nine shots.
I wonder where one of them went.
Look at all the blood.
It's like the perfect crime scene.
Let's get some speed going, then we pick up some blood.
No, wait.
We don't drink blood anymore.
We're done with that.
I need to get that out of my head.
I need water.
I need blood potion.
I can empty that and get water.
Here we go.
I'm speed running.
Someone died here too.
Okay, calm down.
All right, we're speed running this one.
As long as we have acceleration.
Nice, nice.
Kill this guy.
Only I could hit the enemies.
That would be lovely.
What's up, Hamis?
We high fived on the way there.
How did I not get poisoned there?
Or toxic?
Now it's your turn.
Give me that one.
Gold nog appeared above him.
That's polymorphine!
That's bad.
Don't want that in your system.
It's actually one of the most scariest things in the game.
Oh yeah, you're gonna die.
How did I not get hit?
That's incredible.
Not much of anything down here.
A very disappointing hemisphere so far.
I need more of this.
Oh nice, a heart.
That's what I'm talking about.
I am actually gonna grab this tablet.
Thank you.
How did you not die?
And to get in there, I can use a bomb.
Nope, I can use this one.
There we go.
I'm gonna water myself and head in.
Damn it, the heart fell.
300 monies.
I'm getting impatient and that's bad.
You know, I just want to hit through the portal and move on, but...
Probably not a good idea.
Do not get impatient.
The Huerta there.
Okay.
Just get in there.
Ah, burning Huerta.
No, that's the hymns.
Okay, so look, he dropped two gold.
Accident?
Because he burned?
And I didn't directly kill him?
Is that what's happening?
But what is trick then?
There's also trick money or whatever.
I wonder what that means.
Uh, whiskey?
No.
No, thank you.
Let's go.
What do I got?
A good old chainsaw.
And...
Protectile repulsion sector.
Or this one.
More love.
Creatures become more friendly towards each other.
Um, let me see here.
I probably want that one and that one.
So I still have a bunch of money left.
I could reroll, but this one is also kind of cool, right?
Protectiles that fly into a small sector in front of you get blown away.
Let's try that.
I don't think I've tried this one, but I have tried another field that rejects projectiles.
Oh yeah, look at this.
That's actually pretty dope.
I can aim it like...
Oh, something's coming from the right.
Quickly do that.
Very cool.
Uh, give me this.
Let's see what I got.
How does that work?
Runs out super fast.
Terrible.
Not bad.
Not bad at all, but runs out of mana quick.
But recharge is quick as well.
Interesting how that changes.
Why does that change anything?
Okay.
Hold on a second.
So this one reduces recharge time by 0.70.
If I have nothing here, I need to confirm this, man.
I'm limited by recharge because you can see the bar in the top right.
Right.
Yeah, and that makes sense too.
But when I put this in here, it's the same.
It is shooting the chainsaw though.
It's alternating, of course, as expected.
But if I do this...
Wait, what's happening?
Well, why can't I see the other thing being done here?
I don't understand.
When I'm finally done with this game, by the way, I'm going to ask you guys about this, because this thing is BREAKING MY BRAIN!
It's insane.
Shit makes no sense.
It's actually driving me crazy.
And when I finally think I understand it, it does something crazy, you know?
And it doesn't make any sense anymore.
Okay, watch this.
This is going to be the craziest kill.
Ready?
What the fuck?
Why are there so many?
What's happening here?
Oh, there's a nest right there.
I see.
Uh-oh.
That's...
The projection repulsion field is actually working really subtly.
Wow.
Yo, that's dope.
Not bad at all.
We got to take care of the nest, though.
Otherwise, these guys keep coming back.
Is it also rejecting liquids?
No, it's not.
I don't think so, at least.
Nice.
All right.
Cleansed.
I'm actually loving this perk!
I think I've been sleeping on it.
Very nice.
Okay.
Wow, even shotgun shells!
I thought they maybe would have been too quick.
Okay, that hit me.
Oh my god, I can't hit shit.
I gotta be honest.
So, the field itself is actually messing with me.
Like, it's fucking up my aim, somehow.
Because it's, like, distracting to look at.
That's the only thing.
Okay, there's a wand there.
We're in pheromone.
I'm gonna get in here.
Dynamite.
In random directions.
Lovely.
Or is it?
Wait, why is it so fast?
What?
It is not...
Oh, it's shuffled!
Never mind.
That's why...
I was like, why doesn't that throw them in a random direction?
The shuffle got me once again.
The...
The oldest bamboozle in the book.
Um...
Yes!
I have ideas.
Like, I can do stuff like this.
And if shit gets too hot, I'm back.
I don't know about that.
I'm unsure about that one.
But I can definitely use it to go through portals.
I'm, like, 99.99% sure.
Whoo!
Yeah, it definitely does reject.
Shoot me.
Wait, he can't see right above him?
Like, dogs.
They can't look up.
How are you not dead?
Hit you, like, five times!
Little asshole.
Yep.
Thank you.
Okay.
Got a little hoodlum.
You know, the way he looks, the best word I can just say is hoodlum.
He looks like a hoodlum to me.
Ono, ono!
He's throwing lava that insane...
Wait, what is that in the back?
Huh?
Hell slime?
What the fuck does that mean?
Look, hell slime.
And he died in lava.
Hell slime?
I have never seen that.
I gotta say, the weapon I have right now is not that great either.
Like, look at this.
They didn't take a million shots.
Uh, give me some water.
That'll do.
You know what?
Just use that on them.
For those big guys, just use the big weaponry.
It's fine.
It's totally okay.
I'm gonna leave him alone.
Shoot me.
It did not repulse!
What is the sham?
Fucking scam field.
I'm going in.
Sometimes it does, sometimes it doesn't.
I think if the projectile is slow enough, it can.
So maybe if I...
The reason it sometimes got blown away is because I was further away and the projectile slowed down during its path.
And when it finally reached me, it had a lower velocity.
And that's why it got repulsed.
That's my theory at least.
Holy shit!
Holy luminous drill!
What is this crap?
Worm attractor?
Why do I like that?
I don't like any of this.
Point!
Revenge explosion!
Ooh, no.
Revenge rats?
Never skip leg day.
You kick, steal extra damage and knock back.
Why not?
We're going out kicking.
That's a decent want.
I may take it.
That's not that great.
It's okay for certain things, I guess.
Let me add this.
Can we do this?
Yeah, I don't know.
It's not bad.
It's like workable.
It can work.
Now, do I have anything that can kill a god?
Maybe eggs.
Oh, wait.
What?
What do you mean not enough gold?
Oh, I was looking.
I keep looking up here and thinking that's my gold.
That's my HP.
I'm such an idiot.
Point two.
Hold on.
And that was kind of shite.
Do that.
I mean, that's okay.
It's not amazing or anything, but it'll do the job.
This one, though, won't.
This is actually shit want.
I'm gonna get my ass kicked now.
I really wanna make a hole right here and fight the dude.
I gotta be honest.
I cannot handle not being able to change my wants.
It's just such a bummer.
I'm gonna try and kill him with that.
This is gonna be my method of kill.
We're gonna try.
Hold on.
Maybe I can make it better.
If that is my actual damage.
See, that's dope.
If I get in close, run away.
Recharge, come back.
Run away, you know.
That's what I'm gonna do.
Okay, that's the plan.
Uh, yeah.
All right.
Wish me luck.
Here we go, here we go.
I'm stuck, I'm stuck.
Hey, oh yeah, oh no, oh no.
Bro, why does the fucking repulsion field only reject some of them?
I don't get it.
What kind of a shit scam perk is that?
Like, it works sometimes, and then it doesn't?
I don't get it?
The kind... what is that?
Doesn't make any sense.
It's like there's an internal cooldown on it or something.
That wasn't in the fine print.
That's a goddamn lie.
And all
I got now was a spitter bolt.
That's fine.
Actually, the spitter bolt is dope.
Don't knock the spitter bolt.
A spitter bolt.
Strikes again.
I hate the gods.
I hate them so much.
I need to find a way to kill...
I know how to do it.
Guys, it's obvious.
It's been under my nose the entire time.
We're getting the tablet.
And then we set up an ambush.
And then we fuck him.
The tablet is the answer.
I'm grabbing that tablet right now.
We got work to do.
That's the way.
And you know what else?
Next time, I'm gonna anger the god from the left side first.
Such that I can prepare the ambush when he comes towards me.
I should have thought about that.
Why did I dig on the right side?
I don't have enough time.
I should have...
Oh, man.
Okay.
It's fine.
All I see is red right now.
We gotta go kill the god.
I don't care.
We're angering the gods as soon as we can in this run.
I need to get over my fear of this.
It needs to happen.
Need to find a reliable method of murder.
And what's more, I need to be able to get away with that murder.
Untraceable.
No DNA left behind.
Everything above board.
Let's not go that way.
Why is everything so crazy here?
Insane monsters are waiting at my doorstep.
Uh,
nope.
Oh, god.
I have an- Oh!
A wand for me.
I can't get in.
Oh, but I can.
Let's do that.
Oh, no.
Blood me.
Oh, yeah, I'm bloody.
Fireball?
Uh, not bad.
I'll take it.
Actually decent.
And blood does not work on that, I have to remember.
I cannot use blood.
I use water.
Don't you fucking shoot me in the face.
I shoot you in the face.
I am fueled by anger, right?
Like, I am fueled.
I am ready for a fight.
I'm itching, dude.
All over my body.
The itch is real.
This guy is going down.
We gotta name him.
We gotta come up with a name for this guy.
Because he's always the same guy.
I'm gonna call him Troy.
No, his name is Sed.
That way, whenever I kill him, I can say Sed's dead, baby.
His name is Sed.
I can't get in there.
Really?
Oh, wait, I have this.
Get him.
No!
One thing I didn't want to happen.
Oh, it's fine.
By the way, there's something I've noticed about the fire.
I think it burns proportionally to the HP you have.
So like...
Because think about it like this.
I don't take very much damage when I burn now.
But when I have like 500 HP, I burn for way more.
So it's like a percentage.
So...
Fire is actually...
Always the same amount of deadly in a way.
Like no matter where you are.
Like it never gets less deadly.
If you know what I mean.
Pheromone!
Hey!
Let's go.
What's happened here?
Why is everything so...
I don't even know how to describe it.
The collapsed mines.
Load up.
Show me the hearts.
Show me the goods.
Oh no, not the froggies.
Ow!
That hurt.
I am gonna blast them.
Lava.
Sir, would you like some lava on that?
Oh, that's some range.
Okay, you know what?
Fuck you.
That's how we do it.
That's the special horta.
Okay, I'm watered, so that's good.
Let's water.
Let's get some blood out of here and get some actual water.
Do not...
Ah, this is fire.
Maybe I'll get rid of the lava.
Just lava it up, baby.
What if I drink lava?
That a stupid question.
Probably, right?
I mean, I could right click it.
I wonder what would happen.
Not doing it though.
Look at this fucker down there.
Oh, I know how to deal with you.
I've got fireballs.
Watch this, baby.
You know what?
Okay then.
Wow.
I'm stuck in the lava!
I couldn't move my character.
That was a pixel of lava in the corner.
What?
No, what a death.
That's horrible.
Oh, what a way to go.
What do we got here?
Polymorphine.
What a way to start.
Incredible.
God, I've died a lot today.
Neutze has not been kind to me on this day.
Another way of saying that is...
I have been pretty shit at the game today.
I've made some pretty undesirable moves.
You know what?
That's not true.
I figured out a lot of stuff.
I got to a whole new region.
I did all that.
That's actually kind of big.
I'm proud of myself.
Not copium.
Hey!
I like that.
In fact, that means we can go grab a heart.
And I'm gonna do it.
You know, believe me, watch.
I will.
What?
Piece of land in the way.
Beautiful.
Incredible.
Let's see if I can do this with one hit of the dynamite.
It needs to be absolutely perfect.
This...
This shot I'm gonna do right now is gonna determine the outcome of the rest of this run.
One shot, one opportunity roll.
I need to line it up.
Need to be perfect here.
Mom's spaghetti.
Come on, come on.
Oh no!
Okay, so that means we're gonna have almost the perfect run.
I'm not superstitious.
So, this basically means we're gonna get very close to achieving our goals in this run, and then just come short.
That's what that means.
And now we have a tablet.
That's a deadly weapon.
So, that means it's time to head over to Sid.
And make him dead.
Because I see red!
What is with these potions?
I don't want fire in my potion.
I want... I want...
I don't know.
Not fire.
I want porridge in my potion.
We're in pheromone.
I don't want that either, but I'll take it.
Just because I'll take it.
Oh no.
That works.
Wait, what's...
Oh, that's polymorphine.
We gotta get rid of it.
Gotta find a container of some sort.
And store it away safely.
It's actually kind of cool.
The way you have to think about that, you know?
I'm actually thinking about ways to safely get rid of the polymorphine.
Because I have a tendency to gravitate towards it.
And get hit by it again and again.
So this is how we do it.
We're gonna turn these guys into sheep.
Come on.
How are you not getting hit by that?
A little higher.
Yes, yes.
A little lower.
Are you actually kidding me?
All right, fine.
We get to die.
Okay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Calm down now.
All right, that works.
Hamis.
Salute the Hamis.
Now I want an emote of a salute with a Hamis.
I feel like that would be appropriate.
Like, whenever you kill a Hamis, you have to give them a short salute.
Thanks for your service, you know?
Now you got to go because you've got money.
That's a wand.
I have dynamite.
Why can't I kick it?
There we go.
Wait, I don't have water.
I forgot about that.
Let's find some.
Wait, what happened to...
Oh yeah, I got rid of my polymorphine.
I think I did it in a safe manner.
That's how we do it.
Somehow I'm owning.
I don't know how, but it's happening.
Oh no.
You know how I told you I would get rid of the polymorphine in a safe manner?
This right here is not what I meant.
I fucked up.
Oh, and there's also some down here.
This is bad.
That's not good.
I really dropped the ball with this one.
Yep, I take full responsibility for that.
Hey, bouncing burst is actually not that bad right now.
I'm usually shitting on it, but this is...
Okay, there's a chest there.
That's nice.
Let's get in.
But the bouncing burst is kind of working here.
Oh, don't get caught on fire.
Can I destroy the chest?
Oh, there was a bomb in there.
That's why you don't go near those things.
Open them from a safe distance.
What is this crap?
Oh nice, it's burning.
It's not burning.
It is burning.
It's going to take a while.
It's not going to take a while.
You know what?
I have a feeling that's going to fall on me and set me on fire.
Stand here and watch it burn.
Hold on, there's also a path here.
There is not.
Oh god.
Yep, that's what I'm talking about.
Let's go.
Path is safe.
Uh oh.
I'm going to dynamite him.
No, I'm not.
I'm going to tablet him.
Come here, come here.
Okay, let's kill the little guy first.
I hate...
Like when he said like this, I can't tablet him.
I just can't.
You mad now?
Come on.
Fuck!
Come on now.
Is he stuck?
What's happening?
What an asshole.
He deflected my tablet midair.
What a guy.
That's how we do it.
Don't forget to pick it up.
Very nice.
Dude, I'm playing smooth right now.
Only lost a single point of HP, baby.
And you know what?
That fits in really well with the whole premonition we had in the beginning.
That this run was going to be almost perfect.
You know, it's not quite there, which means we're not quite at 100 HP.
But it's barely.
99%.
We can't get up there.
Actually, we can.
Like look at these shots.
It's perfection.
TNT would be perfection.
We got to fill up the water bottle here.
I have a feeling I may not get high for a while.
I think I'll need to stay sober for a bit.
It always has a tendency to not work in your favor, I've noticed.
Unless I've just been very unlucky, it just seems like it.
You know, seems like a bad idea to get high.
But it is fun.
Where the hell do I go?
I've been here already.
Ah, wait a minute.
There we go.
Aha!
I got hit again.
I can't even imagine people doing the no hit runs.
It's a thing, apparently.
How the fuck do you play this game without getting hit?
That's, that's, that's...
That blows my mind.
I don't understand.
You must be some kind of god to do that.
Like with all the RNG that happens.
Oh, shit.
Did he die?
Oh, you've got one of those dudes.
He did.
And he died.
To his own weapon, I think.
That's a frog.
I thought it was his projectile jumping around.
That was so confused.
It was green, you know?
Somehow the bouncing burst is killing right now.
What is happening?
This is very unusual.
The bouncing burst is normally not this good.
There's some kind of thing down there.
A horta hiding in the attic?
The hortatic.
Holy HP, Batman.
Don't accidentally fall into the portal now.
There's circular, I'll take that.
Also, I keep forgetting I have a tablet I can use.
But it is, it is kind of hard.
Like that, that is definitely hard to use.
You gotta, you gotta, you gotta be really good with that.
That's for you.
Oh, that's gonna blow, isn't it?
Oh, yeah, he's gonna die.
Mix, mix, mix.
Oh, watch this.
Oh, that's beautiful.
Pure beauty.
Okay, another, wait, he didn't die.
And here's the entrance to the, to the cave.
The cave.
600 gold, sweet.
I'm playing abnormally well.
That's a frog.
I can blow this.
You know what, there's no reason to do this if I can't see in there anyway.
I mean, unless you get all the water out, I guess it is possible to just, you know, walk through it, hoping you get the sort of right spot in, in total darkness, because you can't drown.
It's possible, I guess.
All right, it's time.
Can we anger?
Said.
Oh, yes, we can, baby.
Plasma cuter in the building.
That's shit.
That's also, wow.
I don't know about that one.
I mean, I guess it is a sort of protection, isn't it?
Like if things hit me from behind, they're going to hit me.
It's basically going to absorb things that would otherwise hit me.
Like it's cool, but is it cool enough?
It's like the question, right?
I don't think it is.
Also, how are we going to kill this guy?
Maybe...
Oh, no, that's like the issue here.
Oh, tablet, tablet, of course.
We're going to tablet him.
So this is the plan.
He spawns here.
I'm going to be waiting here, okay?
He comes and I go...
Right on his face.
Just not like that.
I'm going to be a little more to the left.
Good thing I just did a practice.
I'm going to stand like here.
And as soon as he comes, that's how we do it.
Or even here, I can go...
Oh, is that enough though?
I wonder if momentum plays a role.
If I like drop like this,
definitely throws it harder aiming down.
I could also wait for him up here and be like...
Right when he spawns.
Wouldn't that be crazy?
What's that?
Bombs materialized.
Bomb-like spells can be placed in the item space and inventory and used like throwable items.
Huh.
I don't know about that.
I am feeling another re-roll.
I'm getting a bit addicted to the re-rolling.
I do admit.
Oh, but then I can't...
Oh, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Nope, we can't do that.
Shit!
Okay, I guess we're coming back here.
Yeah, that's fine.
Plasma cutter in the bag.
Then I'm going to get...
I guess luminous drill.
No, I don't need that because I have plasma cutter.
Plasma cutter is amazing.
Okay, that's actually pretty dope.
How about here?
Nah, way too little mana.
Terrible.
It's got to be that one.
Although...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's got to be that one.
I mean, bouncing burst is...
Do I not have anything better?
Yeah, that sucks.
Oh, but oh, here's the thing.
If I miss with this...
I think it's over.
Because I'm going to be fumbling around trying to pick it up and he's going to kill me in the meantime.
You just know that's going to happen.
You just know it.
Or I can try with the plasma cutter actually.
Maybe that will...
That'll probably go through a shield.
Hey, it's a possibility, right?
I killed him once with that, but it was kind of a battle.
Okay, here we go.
I could also...
This is basically a tablet, but on command.
Oh, wait a minute.
He absorbed...
No, no, no, wait.
He deflected the rocks last time.
So that's not going to work.
Shit.
Hopefully the same thing won't happen with the tablet.
Oh, no, I'm really nervous.
Okay, contingency.
Let's say I can't get a kill.
I think I just try to leave.
I just go.
Go, go, go, go, go.
You know, get out of here.
I'm going to get the fuck out real fast.
All right, here we go.
Wish me luck.
You believe in me?
Yes or no?
Let me know.
I'm not going to read it, but still, everyone else will.
It's fun.
Here we go.
Let me anger.
Are you mad now, bro?
Oh, you mad now.
You mad.
Yeah, you mad, bro.
Come here.
Oh, you know what?
I...
Oh, he's coming.
Is he?
Sir?
Exquisite me?
Dude, I have an idea.
I have the craziest...
Okay, never mind.
He's coming.
Okay, check this out.
Check this out.
I'm going to make a little bunker where I can hit him, but he can't hit me.
Oh, this is so smart.
I'm a genius.
Hold on.
Don't get hit by the own beam here.
Let's be careful.
I have a genius idea here, guys.
I call it the plasmacotta method.
The PCM.
PCM.
Oh no, oh no.
Okay, okay, here we go.
Okay, okay.
New plan, new plan.
We're going to get him here.
Come on.
I wish you a whole fucking family.
He's having a nice holiday.
God damn it, Sid.
All I want is to edit my wand.
Don't you understand?
I...
It's all I want.
Okay.
I mean...
Okay, actually it's worse.
Fucking sad, dude.
Big C.
Okay.
I feel like the tablet sucks.
Like I hit him with it, didn't do enough damage.
I think I did like 80 damage.
It depends how much momentum it has, right?
I think I should...
Okay.
Next time, if I have a plasmacotta, I'm going to try my PMC method.
We're doing the PMC next time.
And I'm going to pre-make the bunker before I spawn him.
But wait, I can't.
Because when I make the bunker, I anger the gods.
But maybe it will give me enough time.
I'll figure out a way.
You motherfucker.
Oh wait, that's polymorphine.
Somehow I just didn't get...
That was lucky.
I hate this guy.
I hate... I hate Zed so much.
I want to find him and just serve him food that isn't delicious.
You know?
That's how much I hate him.
Let's not go that way.
Okay.
No, that's not water.
Learn, dammit.
Concentrate a man, I'll take that.
I feel like I can't focus on anything right now, people.
I need to... I need to...
I need to brainstorm ways to kill that guy.
Because I've had enough.
It's simply enough.
I can't do it anymore.
It needs to happen.
I need to find reliable methods.
I can always get him out of the picture.
And the biggest problem is his fucking shield.
Mmm, not bad.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Maybe there's something I can do with the Homebringer spell.
Or the one where I go back in time.
Maybe there's something...
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
What if...
Ooh.
I just had an idea.
What if the new standard is to...
I've actually thought about this before.
But how about we start by going to the snowy depths.
And we just sort of avoid enemies, pretty much.
And just collect some wands.
So we get some kind of spell.
Just any spell, really.
And we need to have like a list in our minds of a spell that can easily kill the guy.
You know?
So when we get to the Holy Mountain, we can edit the wand.
Fix up the thing we need with the spell.
We can always go back up, right?
And that will ensure that we can get through all the Holy Mountains without ever collapsing them.
But, I mean, of course it relies on luck a little bit and what we find.
But maybe...
Why can I not go to the right?
There's got to be a path to the right here.
I'm losing my mind.
Maybe up here.
That looks better.
Shit!
Oh, yeah, good.
Nice.
Perfect.
I'm burning, and I have polymorphine.
Oh, wait, wait.
Mana, mana, mana, mana.
That works.
Yeah, now it's going to be even harder to get where I want to go.
Oh, a wand here.
I think I already tried a black hole against the guy.
Didn't do anything.
Very nice!
You know what that means, right?
That wand is not bad.
I'm going to switch out this one, I think.
You have been promoted to my main damage wand.
Spitter bolt.
Oh, come on.
Okay.
And the good news is, if I can get to the cave, I can heal up.
And then we can go down into the snowy depths.
Is
that actually...
wow.
You know what?
Wasn't there some health over here somewhere as well?
I'm just going to quickly confirm.
I feel like there was some kind of orb somewhere.
It's been a while, but there was something somewhere.
Hold on, let me actually see my map again.
Yeah, so I'm like here.
Oh, you can't see my mouse.
I'm like, whoops.
There, right now.
Approximately.
So there's a pyramid and then some kind of lookout tower.
With another music thingy.
This one contained...
Oh, I should have marked this.
I forgot to mark it.
I'm pretty sure it contained a drawing, actually.
Of the pond.
Or whatever.
This one.
Oh, you can't see.
With something above it.
Or was that in the pyramid?
Oh, I don't remember.
Fuck it.
Let's go.
Let's fill out the map now, actually, if I discover what's there.
The only thing is, can I even get in the pyramid?
That's like the question.
Let's just quickly have a look-see.
So peaceful up here, I love it.
There's no killing.
No bloodshed.
No anger.
No said.
Fucking gods throwing a temper tantrum.
The desert.
Air feels hot.
So basically,
is that gonna evaporate that?
Or maybe not.
Oh, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Mushroom?
Down, down.
Oh my god, the music jump-scared me.
Um, mushroom, down, down.
It could mean that there's something down below.
I mean, there's always something down below, so it's not really a surprise, is it?
Maybe there's one above, two below.
Or something.
Or maybe I need to bring a mushroom here and place it on this pedestal.
And then something will happen down there.
Probably not.
I'm imagining things.
Don't you shoot me with your little shotgun, you.
Is it getting darker?
And what the hell is this?
Hold on.
I never marked this.
This is always here.
Bone wall.
I feel like I made my map a little too small.
There's way more distance.
Hold on, let's actually do that.
Let me, uh, something like that.
There's definitely more.
Goes like that.
And then there's a huge fucking skull in the ground.
So let's, let's make it here.
Maybe not that big, actually.
It is big, but not that big.
So what does it look like?
Some kind of...
huge animal, for sure.
With a huge eye.
Okay.
So what I'm going to do is just sort of draw it.
Something like that.
I'm not the best at drawing.
I was pretty good at drawing once, though, when I was a child, but not anymore.
I'm gonna write something here.
Huge skull.
Okay.
Very cool.
Meanwhile, the sun has set, it seems.
And it has become night.
Good thing we have a, uh, torch, huh?
Let's go exploring.
So here we go.
That's the pyramid.
So the bone thing is actually quite close to the pyramid.
I can't get in there, unfortunately.
I don't have any ways to dig.
Maybe it's a good refresher to just quickly take a trip through the landscape here, you know?
Yes!
There it is.
Orb of true knowledge.
So let me do that.
It sort of makes a, uh,
something like that.
And we have green.
It's a tablet.
And we have a heart.
Plus.
Okay.
Very cool.
Actually good to know.
Look at this!
How is that not special?
Yeah, someone's angry.
Okay.
I think I've had enough.
I'm gonna go back to, uh, the hemisphere now.
There's also the huge tower on the right, but I can't do anything there.
I need to be able to dig to get in there.
I don't have the means for that.
So we head back.
And I think it has become morning.
I mean, I have this, but I don't think that's gonna dig anything.
Actually, this may.
No, I'm going back.
We got the health!
We got the health I came for.
Everything's cool.
I feel like there's gotta be something I can do here with this thing.
What's down here?
What if I put this here?
Also, what does this one say again?
The necessity of concealing the art.
Oh, wait a minute.
Is this saying the necessity of concealing the location?
Like the one of the sub areas?
Concealing the art is one of the chief anxieties of alchemists.
We are sworn to secrecy by heaven and earth and hell.
By the four elements, by the height and depth, by Hermes, by Anubis, and by the howlings of Cercoras.
Oh,
I heard a sound, but it's actually just this polymorphine making the sound.
Shouldn't have spilled that there, and that's a mistake.
An oath has been required of us to reveal nothing clearly to any uninitiated being.
Emerald tablet of Thoth.
I don't know how to pronounce that.
Heaven and hell.
Okay, so I know there's stuff up in the heaven, and I know there's a place with hellrock or hellstone.
Which was like this mini dungeon type deal that I completed, remember?
Heaven and hell.
Wait, no, this is not where I entered over here.
Nope, not quite there yet.
I think the entrance was here.
Yeah, I definitely made this distance on the map way too short.
Like I've been walking forever.
Like that skull was like right next to the pyramid, basically.
I completely misjudged the distance on that when I drew it.
I was doing it for memory at the time, and it was quite a while since I've been up there.
Right.
Back to it, back to it.
In fact, we even have what it takes to go grab the other heart.
On top of the mountain.
Not a bad start to grab some extra HP here.
If anything, it's gonna help us in the fight against Zed.
Big C.
Actually, hold on, in English, I think it's called Big Zed.
Funnily enough, like the name Zed, Zed E.D.
is pronounced the same way, just the letter Zed.
It's a bit odd.
Okay, I can use this.
Or that.
I'm gonna use this to get up here.
That did almost nothing.
There we go.
No, we didn't go.
We didn't go anywhere.
Now we went somewhere.
Now we use this.
Nice.
There we go.
Solid start.
And you know what?
Look at this.
We could even go murder a worm.
And then we would have...
No, wait, we don't need that, because we have torch!
Never mind!
What am I...
The fuck am I talking about?
I'm an idiot.
We don't need that.
That's why we have the torch.
Jesus.
Someone's angry again.
I do wonder what happens if you...
I'm stuck.
What happens if you pick up too many of these orbs?
How many orbs are there, I wonder?
Like, the fact...
I've said this before, but the fact that the game tracks it like this...
It's one of the main UI elements.
And it hasn't had any effect on my game at all so far in my time in this game.
Like, it's got to mean something big, and I cannot even fathom what that could be.
It's blowing my mind a little bit.
Unless there is nothing to do with it, and it's just like a...
Hey, I got this many orbs.
I'm awesome.
I don't know.
There's a wand.
Covered in sludge.
How dare you.
I gotta find water.
Oh man, I was at the pond!
Why didn't I pick it up?
How did I miss?
There we go.
Much better.
There's way too much toxic shit here.
If this pleases me.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, there buddy.
You have a wand, huh?
Is that a flamethrower or what is that?
Nope.
Why do I always end up with 16 HP?
That's happened like three or four times today.
Um, do I want this at all?
No, I don't.
I mean, yes, maybe I do.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, take it.
Take it.
I gotta play super careful until we get to the cave.
Please don't mess it up now.
Water.
Let's get rid of chaotic polymorphine plus toxic sludge.
What a combination.
A combination nobody has ever enjoyed.
I actually really loved chaotic polymorphine when I started this game.
Now I hate it.
I thought it was so cool I can transform into anything.
Until I realized it kind of sucks being other things.
Let me dispose of this somewhere else safely.
I don't even know what to put it.
Maybe here.
That works.
Let me grab the water.
And then I'm going to go convert the pool on the right to water as well.
We can get even more water and a wand.
Okay.
All we need.
I'm going to give it more though.
Speed it up a bit.
Disc projectiles.
I like it.
I'm going to take it.
Am I though?
No, actually.
I don't want to replace anything I have.
I really like everything I have.
I'll probably replace the torch when I'm done with this place.
Yeah, that's what I'm going to do.
Uh-oh.
Um.
This can get a little scary.
The collapsed mo- Look at that!
Where did all this water- Pipes?
What?
I've never seen that before.
What the hell?
Oh, there's a frog right there.
Oh, there's a frog right there too.
Oh my god, they're so stealthy.
Hmm.
Little stealthy frogs.
There's a big frog there.
Uh-oh.
Oh, there's a whole family of frogs.
One down.
Two down.
And the next- last one is going to get the explosive treatment.
That's right, bitch!
Everyone's going to burn alive now and everyone loves it.
Uh-oh.
This thing right here is scary.
Let me water myself.
What is in here?
Hmm.
If this guy's going to come back from the right, I'm fucked.
It's actually kind of dangerous.
Okay.
All the- Oh!
Come on.
Sir.
Bye-bye.
That was great.
Let's see it.
Dynamite?
Could be good.
Uh...
Yeah, I don't have any more of these anyway.
That guy's over there.
That doesn't please me at all.
Where did all this water come from?
I don't mind though.
I like water.
Water's good.
Okay, I'm in the spot.
Now I just got to be really careful.
There's still a couple dudes over here.
Say, dudes, you like this?
Don't even think about it.
I will take that money.
Okay.
I kind of want to enter from up top there.
So I'm going to make a hole here.
Come here, Horta.
16 HP, baby.
That's all a man needs.
We've got torch.
Oh, but hold on.
We may need to drain a little bit.
That is a long swim.
A long swim.
There's already so much water here though.
Of course, we've got to make a hole here.
We murdered this dude.
We make a hole here.
We got to drain more though.
Oh, that was scary.
Now we just wait a bit for this to drain out, and then we go in with our torch.
The plan is coming to fruition.
Look at that.
Hey, huh?
Sweet.
Can we make the swim?
We cannot.
We have to wait a bit.
I've got to wait for this to drain all the way out.
Unless I can.
Oh wait, I can probably make a hole here somewhere.
I see anything over here.
Go.
Go, go, go, go, go.
I'm committed.
No, don't!
No!
I'm so ashamed!
Why did I do it?
What did I do?
That's terrible, man.
All that prep...
Wait, was that only 25 minutes?
That felt like an hour.
Really?
That's blowing my mind a little bit.
How was that only 25 minutes?
I went...
Like, I explored the hemisphere.
I went up.
Then I explored the pyramid.
I did all kinds of shit up there.
Then I came back and I spent the...
How the fuck?
Okay, that's weird.
Wow.
But look at that.
We had a sick amount of max HP in the first level.
Yep.
How the fuck did I ever accrue 1,745?
What happened that run?
Jesus.
Okay.
Well, I'm gonna end it there.
Because it's time for me to get some food.
It's been a while since I ate.
I ate right before I started streaming.
Let me switch it over to this.
Exquisite me.
Oh no.
Oh?
It's playing this again.
I have an idea.
Remove it!
Off you go!
There we go.
It's gone.
For those that missed it, I played a little compilation of all my deaths in the beginning of the stream.
It was really nice.
How's everybody doing, huh?
I'm sorry about that last death, man.
I'm ashamed.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
I got more montage material.
That's true.
That's the silver lining to that, for sure.
Definitely.
What's up, everybody?
Mr. Beat, hello.
Liminal roar.
Fun stream, though.
Lots of things learned, for sure.
Especially towards, like, the first part of the stream.
I would say the first half, I learned a lot.
But also actually the second half.
Mostly the first half, though.
You're playing the game right way.
Don't worry about dying, trying to figure out solutions to your problem.
I don't worry too much about dying.
It's just a little sad when it happens.
But I always look forward to the next run.
Like, I'm surprised this game is still this entertaining, after all this time.
Like, I've done a lot of the same stuff again and again.
But somehow, it's still interesting.
When you finally found out Lumi's potential, we were screaming at you to use it, what felt like hours.
Oh!
Man, I felt like...
I don't even know how many hours I've played this game.
Let me check Steam.
So I've played this for 94 hours now, guys.
94 hours.
And all of those hours, except one, I did not realize that the luminous drill could go through brickwork.
I thought it was crap.
Yeah.
You live, you learn, I guess.
You were screaming at me last stream?
Oh, well, that's not unusual.
It happens every stream, I think.
When you go through your videos, do you see the chat?
Yeah, I do, but I don't look at it.
Like, it's just there in the bottom left, you know?
It's basically like a blob of things just scrolling.
Yeah, you said you will ask us when you stop playing.
There's like a million stuff we want to show you.
And this game became fun for me after learning some stuff, actually.
Yeah, I mean, at some point, we're gonna probably do a wrap up stream for this game.
Unless, hold on, I'm actually not sure about that, because this is the type of game I would come back to on my own, either on stream or off stream in the future.
Like, this is the type of game I would jump into.
Like, let's say I'm not playing it all the time, full time or whatever.
I would just jump in a couple times a week just to play it because I get the itch.
And I would love to just keep exploring and expand the map.
No, you know?
So this is one of those games that can take a long time, I think.
It's a slow burn, but it's fun, I think.
Yeah, I've wrapped up stream at some point for sure.
I mean, probably a long time in the future, though.
But it would be fun.
There's some stuff I guarantee you will basically never find.
I believe it.
And that's okay.
I don't expect to find everything.
That is totally okay.
I've made peace with that long, many, many years ago.
The Noiter itch.
Exactly, Frank.
It's real.
For me, the game that gives me itches the most is Isaac.
Yo, Binding of Isaac?
My real life friend has played like 400 hours of that and he says it's amazing.
I haven't tried it yet myself.
But it is one of those games where I think I've seen some screenshots from it and some gameplay and it just doesn't seem that fun.
But then again, I would probably say the same about Noiter back before I played this.
And, you know, so I shouldn't say too much.
I should try the things.
You have 1200 hours in Isaac.
You have 920.
Hey, that's a good number, though.
920.
Cool.
I love that little gif.
I found that, by the way, on 7TV.
I don't know exactly what's going on in that.
Is that like a little hamster underneath one of those ventilators or whatever?
What is it supposed to represent?
I just thought it was really funny.
Your map are real nice?
Hey, thank you, man.
I try my best to make it at least look a little nice, too.
I mean, I intentionally don't make it very detailed or textured or anything.
It's just outlines, you know?
But I think that's fine.
I'm not an artist in any way.
I do what I can.
I literally had the same feeling about Isaac, but when I finally got into it, I realized it got so much deeper.
Yeah, I believe it.
I believe it.
Like, there's so many games that I've been mentally shitting on until I tried them, and I've been blown away by them.
So, yeah, at this point, I shouldn't even judge anything.
Don't judge a book by its cover.
I tended to do that a lot before I even played Hollow Knight.
I thought all 2D games were a little...
I don't know.
It's not as fun.
I was wrong, man.
I was wrong.
I had so much fun with Hollow Knight.
My first, like, real big 2D game that I played.
Like, I've played Worms and stuff in the past, and that was fun, you know?
Your dad is more of a giga chat.
He has 7,300 hours.
Team Fortress 2.
Holy shit.
Your dad sounds awesome.
My dad only plays games like...
Oh, what's it called?
World of Warships or something.
You know, stuff like that.
Eradja.
Found your Neuter YouTube videos.
First time seeing you live.
Thank you for many good hours.
Hey, you're welcome.
I'm glad you enjoyed.
Good to see you.
Have you played Red Dead Redemption 2?
I have not played it.
I want to play the first one first, but as far as I know, it's only for...
PlayStation 3.
And there's rumors that it will be remade, right?
For PC, so I'm waiting for that.
Your dad is our customer.
Wait, what do you mean?
Do you work for World of Warships?
Or what do you mean it, Levi?
Would you ever play Noise of PvP someday?
When you're done on the game...
Wait, is there PvP in this game?
That sounds insane.
Not Warships specifically, but same company, yeah.
It's the same company that made...
Is it the same company that made War Thunder?
No, World of Tanks, right?
Kind of surprised to see Elden Ring on your backlog.
So here's the thing, Palicado.
I already played like the first...
I don't remember exactly how many hours.
I want to say between 5 and 10 hours of Elden Ring.
So for those that haven't played the game, mute for a second.
But like, let's say the first area you enter...
And you know what I mean if you've played the game, right?
The first area you enter into.
I think I've explored like maybe like 60% of that area.
50%, it's hard to say.
But I was just wandering around and I stopped because I had other things to do and I couldn't really get into it too much.
And when I play like a Souls game like that, I want to go full on out, you know?
So yeah, I can't wait to play the rest of that.
But I mean, Palicado, I've played all the other Souls game pretty much.
Except the very first Demon Souls.
I haven't played that yet.
But I've played Dark Souls 1, 2 and 3.
I've played Bloodborne now.
I have played Sekiro.
What else have they made?
That's pretty much it, right?
Yeah, I've played all those and they're awesome.
It's super, super fun, amazing.
Oh, it's a mod.
Oh, I was about to say I didn't see that option in the game.
Could be a fun thing to do like a community type stream.
Will you play any more Switch games?
For sure.
No, I mean, I'm also going to play the next Zelda game at some point, Frank.
I just don't know when.
But Zelda was definitely the game that I wanted to get the Switch for.
Just to play that.
That was like the driving factor.
Also want to play the Mario game for that.
Lies of P. Isn't that...
That's not from Fromsoft though.
That's someone else.
But it is a Souls-like.
Which bosses have I found in Noidsa?
So I've killed the last boss.
I've beat the game, basically.
I have beaten the game.
I found the boss in the first area.
And well, I don't know which ones are considered bosses, I guess.
But I have found a big worm inside an egg.
Somewhere.
I think I found a boss today.
A triangle boss, if that makes sense.
And what else have I found?
I think maybe I found something on the surface at some point.
But it disappeared.
Oh, and then I also found one in the ancient laboratory.
Yeah, I guess people in the chat know better.
I can't remember the shit.
Where do I find all this backlog?
I'm gonna link it to you.
There it is.
You beat dragon?
Wait, what dragon?
Did I?
Are you sure?
I don't remember a dragon.
Health bar equals boss.
Okay, okay.
Gotcha.
Oh, the dragon cave!
Oh, okay, yeah.
For me, that's just...
It looks like a worm.
So that's what I meant when I said worm.
Yeah.
I see what you mean now.
Makes sense.
Okay, I'm gonna go make some dinner.
And enjoy the rest of my Friday.
And I hope you will too.
Enjoy the rest of your Friday, I mean.
So thank you for watching, guys.
And also, Quantum.
Thank you for gifting your community sub.
I just noticed that.
And thank you to everyone else for checking it out and following.
I'm gonna send you off to another streamer.
Okay?
Someone streaming Noita.
Let's see here.
Same category.
What do we got?
Let's rate Snake Gregory.
He also rates me sometimes.
Let's return to favor here.
Okay, I'm gonna send you guys over.
Thanks for watching.
Have a good time.
Bye-bye.